<root>
  <data name="IDS_NOFREESPACE_TEXT">
    <value>Your selected storage device doesn't have enough free space to create a game save.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_OVERWRITESAVE_TEXT">
    <value>Your selected storage device already contains this save.  Is it OK to overwrite it?</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_STORAGEDEVICEPROBLEM_TITLE">
    <value>Storage Device Problem</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_FAILED_TO_SAVE_TEXT">
    <value>Your storage device is unavailable or has an error</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_FAILED_TO_LOADSAVE_TEXT">
    <value>Your storage device is unavailable or has an error. Please select a new storage device.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_SELECTANEWDEVICE">
    <value>Select a new storage device</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_NODEVICE_TITLE">
    <value>No storage device selected</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_NODEVICE_TEXT">
    <value>If you do not select a storage device, game saves will be disabled</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_NODEVICE_ACCEPT">
    <value>Select a storage device</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_DEVICEGONE_TEXT">
    <value>Your storage device has been removed.  Please select a new one.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_WARNING_ARCADE_TITLE">
    <value>Return to Xbox Dashboard</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_RETURNEDTOTITLESCREEN_TEXT">
    <value>You have been returned to the title screen because your gamer profile was signed out</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_RETURNEDTOMENU_TEXT">
    <value>The match has ended because a gamer profile was signed out</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_NOTONLINE_TITLE">
    <value>Gamer profile not online</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_NOTONLINE_TEXT">
    <value>This game has some features which require an Xbox Live enabled gamer profile, but you are currently offline.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_XBOXLIVE_NOTIFICATION">
    <value>This feature requires a gamer profile which is signed into Xbox Live.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_NOTONLINE_ACCEPT">
    <value>Connect to Xbox Live</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_ACHIEVEMENTPROBLEM_TITLE">
    <value>Achievement Award Problem</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_ACHIEVEMENTPROBLEM_TEXT">
    <value> There was a problem accessing your gamer profile. Your achievement could not be awarded at this time.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_NOPROFILE_TITLE">
    <value>Gamer profile problem</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_NOPROFILEOPTIONS_TEXT">
    <value>Saving of settings to gamer profile has failed.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_GUESTPROFILE_TITLE">
    <value>Guest Gamer Profile</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_GUESTPROFILE_TEXT">
    <value>Guest gamer profile cannot access this feature. Please use a different gamer profile.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_UNLOCKGAME_TEXT">
    <value>
      This is the Minecraft trial game. If you had the full game, you would just have earned an achievement!
      Unlock the full game to experience the joy of Minecraft and to play with your friends across the globe through Xbox Live.
      Would you like to unlock the full game?
    </value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_SAVE_TRANSFER_WRONG_VERSION">
    <value>The save file in the save transfer area has a version number that this version doesn't support yet.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_PRO_PROFILEPROBLEM_TEXT">
    <value>You are being returned to the main menu because of a problem reading your profile.</value>
  </data>
</root>