<root>
	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_NEWDLC">
		<value>New Downloadable Content is available! Access it from the Minecraft Store button on the Main Menu.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_SKINPACKS">
		<value>You can change the look of your character with a Skin Pack from the Minecraft Store. Select 'Minecraft Store' on the Main Menu to see what's available.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_2">
		<value>Alter the gamma settings to make the game brighter or darker.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_3">
		<value>If you set the game difficulty to Peaceful, your health will automatically regenerate, and no monsters will come out at night!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_4">
		<value>Feed a bone to a wolf to tame it. You can then make it sit or follow you.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_5">
		<value>You can drop items when in the Inventory menu by moving the cursor off the menu and pressing{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_6">
		<value>Sleeping in a bed at night will fast forward the game to dawn, but all players in a multiplayer game need to sleep in beds at the same time.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_7">
		<value>Harvest pork chops from pigs, and cook and eat them to regain health.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_8">
		<value>Harvest leather from cows, and use it to make armor.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_9">
		<value>If you have an empty bucket, you can fill it with milk from a cow, or water, or lava!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_10">
		<value>Use a hoe to prepare areas of ground for planting.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_11">
		<value>Spiders won't attack you during the day - unless you attack them.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_12">
		<value>Digging soil or sand with a spade is faster than with your hand!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_13">
		<value>Eating cooked pork chops gives more health than eating raw pork chops.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_14">
		<value>Make some torches to light up areas at night. Monsters will avoid the areas around these torches.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_15">
		<value>Get to destinations faster with a minecart and rail!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_16">
		<value>Plant some saplings and they'll grow into trees.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_17">
		<value>Pigmen won't attack you, unless you attack them.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_18">
		<value>You can change your game spawn point and skip to dawn by sleeping in a bed.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_19">
		<value>Hit those fireballs back at the Ghast!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_20">
		<value>Building a portal will allow you to travel to another dimension - The Nether.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_21">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} to drop the item currently in your hand!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_22">
		<value>Use the right tool for the job!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_23">
		<value>If you can't find any coal for your torches, you can always make charcoal from trees in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_24">
		<value>Digging straight down or straight up is not a great idea.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_25">
		<value>Bonemeal (crafted from a Skeleton bone) can be used as a fertilizer, and can make things grow instantly!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_26">
		<value>Creepers explode when they get close to you!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_27">
		<value>Obsidian is created when water hits a lava source block.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_28">
		<value>Lava can take minutes to disappear COMPLETELY when the source block is removed.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_29">
		<value>Cobblestone is resistant to Ghast fireballs, making it useful for guarding portals.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_30">
		<value>Blocks that can be used as a light source will melt snow and ice. This includes torches, glowstone, and Jack-O-Lanterns.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_31">
		<value>Take caution when building structures made of wool in open air, as lightning from thunderstorms can set wool on fire.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_32">
		<value>A single bucket of lava can be used in a furnace to smelt 100 blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_33">
		<value>The instrument played by a note block depends on the material beneath it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_34">
		<value>Zombies and Skeletons can survive daylight if they are in water.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_35">
		<value>Attacking a wolf will cause any wolves in the immediate vicinity to turn hostile and attack you. This trait is also shared by Zombie Pigmen.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_36">
		<value>Wolves cannot enter the Nether.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_37">
		<value>Wolves won't attack Creepers.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_38">
		<value>Chickens lay an egg every 5 to 10 minutes.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_39">
		<value>Obsidian can only be mined with a diamond pickaxe.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_40">
		<value>Creepers are the easiest obtainable source of gunpowder.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_41">
		<value>Placing two chests side by side will make one large chest.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_42">
		<value>Tame wolves show their health with the position of their tail. Feed them meat to heal them.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_43">
		<value>Cook cactus in a furnace to get green dye.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_46">
		<value>Read the What's New section in the How To Play menus to see the latest update information about the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_47">
		<value>Stackable fences are in the game now!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_49">
		<value>Some animals will follow you if you have wheat in your hand.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_50">
		<value>If an animal can't move more than 20 blocks in any direction, it won't despawn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_1">
		<value>Music by C418!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_2">
		<value>Notch has over a million followers on twitter!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_3">
		<value>Not all Swedish people have blonde hair. Some, like Jens from Mojang, even have ginger hair!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_5">
		<value>There will be an update to this game eventually!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_6">
		<value>Who is Notch?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_7">
		<value>Mojang has more awards than staff!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_8">
		<value>Some famous people play Minecraft!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_9">
		<value>deadmau5 likes Minecraft!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_10">
		<value>Do not look directly at the bugs.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_11">
		<value>Creepers were born from a coding bug.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_12">
		<value>Is it a chicken or is it a duck?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_13">
		<value>Were you at Minecon?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_14">
		<value>No-one at Mojang has ever seen junkboy's face.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_15">
		<value>Did you know there's a Minecraft Wiki?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_16">
		<value>Mojang's new office is cool!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_18">
		<value>Minecon 2013 was in Orlando, Florida, USA!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_19">
		<value>.party() was excellent!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_20">
		<value>Always assume rumors are false, rather than assuming they're true!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_BASICS">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : BASICS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Minecraft is a game about placing blocks to build anything you can imagine. At night monsters come out, make sure to build a shelter before that happens.{*B*}{*B*}
Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_LOOK*} to look around.{*B*}{*B*}
Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*} to move around.{*B*}{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_JUMP*} to jump.{*B*}{*B*}
Push{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*} forward twice in rapid succession to sprint. While you hold {*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*} forward, the character will continue to sprint unless they run out of sprint time or the Food Bar has less than{*ICON_SHANK_03*}.{*B*}{*B*}
Hold{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_ACTION*} to mine and chop using your hand or whatever you are holding. You may need to craft a tool to mine some blocks.{*B*}{*B*}
If you are holding an item in your hand, use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to use that item, or press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_DROP*} to drop that item.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_HUD">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : HUD{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
The HUD shows information about your status; your health, your remaining oxygen when you are under water, your hunger level (you need to eat to replenish this), and your armor if you are wearing any. If you lose some health, but have a food bar with 9 or more{*ICON_SHANK_01*} in it, your health will automatically replenish. Eating food will replenish your food bar.{*B*}
The Experience Bar is also shown here, with a numeric value to show your Experience Level, and the bar indicating how many Experience Points are required to increase your Experience Level. Experience Points are gained by collecting the Experience Orbs dropped by mobs when they die, mining certain block types, breeding animals, fishing, and smelting ores in a furnace.{*B*}{*B*}
It also shows the items that are available to use. Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_LEFT_SCROLL*} and{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_RIGHT_SCROLL*} to change the item in your hand.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_INVENTORY">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : INVENTORY{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_INVENTORY*} to view your inventory.{*B*}{*B*}
This screen shows items available for use in your hand, and all the other items that you are carrying. Your armor is also shown here.{*B*}{*B*}
Use{*CONTROLLER_MENU_NAVIGATE*} to move the pointer. Use{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to pick an item under the pointer. If there is more than one item here this will pick them all up, or you can use{*CONTROLLER_VK_X*} to pick up just half of them.{*B*}{*B*}
Move the item with the pointer over another space in the inventory and place it there using{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*}. With multiple items on the pointer, use{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to place them all, or{*CONTROLLER_VK_X*} to place just one.{*B*}{*B*}
If an item you are over is armor, you will be shown a tooltip to enable a quick move of this to the right armor slot in the inventory.{*B*}{*B*}
It is possible to change the color of your Leather Armor by dying it, you can do this in the inventory menu by holding the dye in your pointer, then pressing{*CONTROLLER_VK_X*} whilst the pointer is over the piece you wish to dye.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_CHEST">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : CHEST{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Once you have crafted a Chest, you can place this in the world and then use it with{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to store items from your inventory.{*B*}{*B*}
Use the pointer to move items between your inventory and the chest.{*B*}{*B*}
Items in the chest will be stored there for you to swap back into your inventory again later.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_LARGECHEST">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : LARGE CHEST{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Two chests placed next to each other will be combined to form a Large Chest. This can store even more items.{*B*}{*B*}
It is used in the same way as a normal chest.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_CRAFTING">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : CRAFTING{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
In the Crafting interface, you can combine items from your inventory to create new types of items. Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_CRAFTING*} to open the crafting interface.{*B*}{*B*}
Scroll through the tabs at the top using{*CONTROLLER_VK_LB*} and{*CONTROLLER_VK_RB*} to select the type of item you wish to craft, then use{*CONTROLLER_MENU_NAVIGATE*} to select the item to craft.{*B*}{*B*}
The crafting area shows the items required to craft the new item. Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to craft the item and place it in your inventory.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_CRAFT_TABLE">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : CRAFTING TABLE{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
You can craft larger items using a Crafting Table.{*B*}{*B*}
Place the table in the world and press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to use it.{*B*}{*B*}
Crafting on a table works in the same way as basic crafting, but you have a larger crafting area, and a more varied selection of items to craft.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_FURNACE">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : FURNACE{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
A Furnace allows you to change items by firing them. For example, you can turn iron ore into iron ingots in the furnace.{*B*}{*B*}
Place the furnace in the world and press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to use it.{*B*}{*B*}
You need to put some fuel into the bottom of the furnace, and the item to be fired in the top. The furnace will then fire up and start working.{*B*}{*B*}
When your items have been fired, you can move them from the output area into your inventory.{*B*}{*B*}
If an item you are over is an ingredient or fuel for the furnace, you will be shown tooltips to enable a quick move of this to the furnace. 
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_DISPENSER">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : DISPENSER{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
A Dispenser is used to shoot out items. You will need to place a switch, for example a lever, next to the dispenser to trigger it.{*B*}{*B*}
To fill the dispenser with items press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*}, then move the items that you want to dispense from your inventory into the dispenser.{*B*}{*B*}
Now when you use the switch, the dispenser will shoot out an item.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_BREWING">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : BREWING{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Brewing potions requires a Brewing Stand, which can be built at a crafting table. Every potion starts off with a bottle of water, which is made by filling a Glass Bottle with water from a Cauldron, or a water source.{*B*}
A Brewing Stand has three slots for bottles, so can make three potions at the same time. One ingredient can be used over all three bottles, so always brew three potions at the same time to best use your resources.{*B*}
Putting a potion ingredient in the top position at the Brewing Stand will make a base potion after a short time. This doesn't have any effect by itself, but brewing another ingredient with this base potion will give you a potion with an effect.{*B*}
Once you have this potion you can add a third ingredient to make the effect last longer (using Redstone Dust), be more intense (using Glowstone Dust), or turn into a harmful potion (using a Fermented Spider Eye).{*B*}
You can also add gunpowder to any potion to turn it into a Splash Potion, which can then be thrown. The thrown Splash Potion will cause the potion effect to apply over the area it lands in.{*B*}

The source ingredients for potions are :-{*B*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Nether Wart{*ETW*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Spider Eye{*ETW*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Sugar{*ETW*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Ghast Tear{*ETW*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Blaze Powder{*ETW*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Magma Cream{*ETW*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Glistering Melon{*ETW*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Redstone Dust{*ETW*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Glowstone Dust{*ETW*}{*B*}
* {*T2*}Fermented Spider Eye{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}

You'll need to experiment with combinations of ingredients in order to find out all the different potions you can make.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_ENCHANTMENT">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : ENCHANTING{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
The Experience Points collected when a mob dies, or when certain blocks are mined or smelted in a furnace, can be used to enchant some tools, weapons, armor and books.{*B*}
When a Sword, Bow, Axe, Pickaxe, Shovel, Armor or Book is placed in the slot below the book in the Enchantment Table, the three buttons to the right of the slot will display some enchantments and their Experience Levels costs.{*B*}
If you do not have enough Experience Levels to use some of these, the cost will appear in red, otherwise it will be shown in green.{*B*}{*B*}
The actual enchantment applied is randomly selected based on the cost displayed.{*B*}{*B*}
If the Enchantment Table is surrounded by Bookshelves (up to a maximum of 15 Bookshelves), with a one block gap between the Bookcase and the Enchantment Table, the potency of the enchantments will be increased, and arcane glyphs will be seen coming from the book on the Enchantment Table.{*B*}{*B*}
All the ingredients for an Enchantment Table can be found within the villages in a world, or by mining and cultivation of the world.{*B*}{*B*}
Enchanted Books are used at the Anvil to apply enchantments to items. This gives you more control over which enchantments you would like on your items.{*B*}
</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_FARMANIMALS">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : FARMING ANIMALS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
If you want to keep your animals in the one place, build a fenced area of less than 20x20 blocks and have your animals inside it. This ensures they will still be there when you come back to see them.
</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_BREEDANIMALS">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : BREEDING ANIMALS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
The animals in Minecraft can breed, and will produce baby versions of themselves!{*B*}
To get the animals to breed, you will need to feed them with the right food to get them to go into 'Love Mode'.{*B*}
Feed Wheat to a cow, mooshroom or sheep, Carrots to a pig, Wheat Seeds or Nether Wart to a chicken, or any kind of meat to a wolf, and they'll start looking for another animal of the same species near them that is also in Love Mode.{*B*}
When two animals of the same species meet, and both are in Love Mode, they will kiss for a few seconds, and then a baby animal will appear. The baby animal will follow their parents for a while before growing into a full sized animal itself.{*B*}
After being in Love Mode, an animal will not be able to enter it again for about five minutes.{*B*}
There is a limit on the number of animals it is possible to have in a world, so you may find the animals don't breed when you have a lot of them.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_NETHERPORTAL">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : NETHER PORTAL{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
A Nether Portal allows the player to travel between the Overworld and the Nether world. The Nether world can be used to fast-travel in the Overworld - traveling one block distance in the Nether is equivalent to traveling 3 blocks in the Overworld, so when you build a portal in the Nether world and exit through it, you will be 3 times further away from your entry point.{*B*}{*B*}
A minimum of 10 Obsidian blocks are required to build the portal, and the portal needs to be 5 blocks high by 4 blocks wide by 1 block deep. Once the portal frame is built, the space inside the frame needs to be set on fire to activate it. This can be done using the Flint and Steel item, or the Fire Charge item.{*B*}{*B*}
Examples of portal construction are shown in the picture to the right.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_BANLIST">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : BANNING LEVELS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
If you find offensive content within a level you are playing, you can choose to add the level to your Banned Levels list. 
If you would like to do this, bring up the Pause menu, then press{*CONTROLLER_VK_RB*} to select the Ban Level tooltip. 
When you attempt to join this level in future, you will be notified that the level is in your Banned Levels list, and given the option to remove it from the list and continue into the level, or back out.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_HOSTOPTIONS">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : HOST AND PLAYER OPTIONS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}

{*T1*}Game Options{*ETW*}{*B*}
When loading or creating a world, you can press the "More Options" button to enter a menu that allows more control over your game.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Player vs Player{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When enabled, players can inflict damage on other players. This option only affects Survival mode.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Trust Players{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When disabled, players joining the game are restricted in what they can do. They are not able to mine or use items, place blocks, use doors and switches, use containers, attack players or attack animals. You can change these options for a specific player using the in-game menu.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Fire Spreads{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When enabled, fire may spread to nearby flammable blocks. This option can also be changed from within the game.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}TNT Explodes{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When enabled, TNT will explode when detonated. This option can also be changed from within the game.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Host Privileges{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When enabled, the host can toggle their ability to fly, disable exhaustion, and make themselves invisible from the in-game menu. {*DISABLES_ACHIEVEMENTS*}{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Daylight Cycle{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When disabled, the time of day will not change.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Keep Inventory{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When enabled, players will keep their inventory when they die.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Mob Spawning{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When disabled, mobs will not spawn naturally.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Mob Griefing{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When disabled, prevents monsters and animals from changing blocks (for example, Creeper explosions won't destroy blocks and Sheep won't remove Grass) or picking up items.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Mob Loot{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When disabled, monsters and animals will not drop loot (for example, Creepers won't drop gunpowder).{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Tile Drops{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When disabled, blocks will not drop items when destroyed (for example, Stone blocks won't drop Cobblestone).{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Natural Regeneration{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When disabled, players will not regenerate health naturally.{*B*}{*B*}

{*T1*}World Generation Options{*ETW*}{*B*}
When creating a new world there are some additional options.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Generate Structures{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When enabled, structures such as Villages and Strongholds will generate in the world.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Superflat World{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When enabled, a completely flat world will be generated in the Overworld and in the Nether.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Bonus Chest{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When enabled, a chest containing some useful items will be created near the player spawn point.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Reset Nether{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When enabled, the Nether will be re-generated. This is useful if you have an older save where Nether Fortresses were not present.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T1*}In-Game Options{*ETW*}{*B*}
	While in the game a number of options can be accessed by pressing {*BACK_BUTTON*} to bring up the in-game menu.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Host Options{*ETW*}{*B*}
	The host player, and any players set as moderators can access the "Host Option" menu. In this menu they can enable and disable fire spreading and TNT exploding.{*B*}{*B*}

{*T1*}Player Options{*ETW*}{*B*}
To modify the privileges for a player, select their name and press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to bring up the player privileges menu where you can use the following options.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Can Build And Mine{*ETW*}{*B*}
	This option is only available when "Trust Players" is turned off. When this option is enabled, the player is able to interact with the world as normal. When disabled the player will not be able to place or destroy blocks, or interact with many items and blocks.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Can Use Doors and Switches{*ETW*}{*B*}
	This option is only available when "Trust Players" is turned off. When this option is disabled, the player will not be able to use doors and switches.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Can Open Containers{*ETW*}{*B*}
	This option is only available when "Trust Players" is turned off. When this option is disabled, the player will not be able to open containers, such as chests.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Can Attack Players{*ETW*}{*B*}
	This option is only available when "Trust Players" is turned off. When this option is disabled the player will not be able to cause damage to other players.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Can Attack Animals{*ETW*}{*B*}
	This option is only available when "Trust Players" is turned off. When this option is disabled the player will not be able to cause damage to animals.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Moderator{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When this option is enabled, the player is able to change privileges for other players (except the host) if "Trust Players" is turned off, kick players and they can enable and disable fire spreading and TNT exploding.{*B*}{*B*}
	
	{*T2*}Kick Player{*ETW*}{*B*}
	{*KICK_PLAYER_DESCRIPTION*}{*B*}{*B*}

{*T1*}Host Player Options{*ETW*}{*B*}
If "Host Privileges" is enabled the host player can modify some privileges for themselves. To modify the privileges for a player, select their name and press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to bring up the player privileges menu where you can use the following options.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Can Fly{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When this option is enabled, the player is able to fly. This option is only relevant to Survival mode, as flying is enabled for all players in Creative mode.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Disable Exhaustion{*ETW*}{*B*}
	This option only affects Survival mode. When enabled, physical activities (walking/sprinting/jumping etc.) do not decrease the food bar. However, if the player becomes injured, the food bar will slowly decrease while the player is healing.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Invisible{*ETW*}{*B*}
	When this option is enabled, the player is not visible to other players and is invulnerable.{*B*}{*B*}

	{*T2*}Can Teleport{*ETW*}{*B*}
	This allows the player to move players or themselves to other players in the world.
</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_NEXT">
		<value>Next Page</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_PREV">
		<value>Previous Page</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_BASICS">
		<value>Basics</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_HUD">
		<value>HUD</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_INVENTORY">
		<value>Inventory</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_CHESTS">
		<value>Chests</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_CRAFTING">
		<value>Crafting</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_FURNACE">
		<value>Furnace</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_DISPENSER">
		<value>Dispenser</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_FARMANIMALS">
		<value>Farming Animals</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_BREEDANIMALS">
		<value>Breeding Animals</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_BREWING">
		<value>Brewing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_ENCHANTMENT">
		<value>Enchantment</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_NETHERPORTAL">
		<value>Nether Portal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_MULTIPLAYER">
		<value>Multiplayer</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_SOCIALMEDIA">
		<value>Sharing Screenshots</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_BANLIST">
		<value>Banning Levels</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_CREATIVE">
		<value>Creative Mode</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_HOSTOPTIONS">
		<value>Host and Player Options</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_TRADING">
		<value>Trading</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_ANVIL">
		<value>Anvil</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_THEEND">
		<value>The End</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_THEEND">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : THE END{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
The End is another dimension in the game, which is reached through an active End Portal. The End Portal can be found in a Stronghold, which is deep underground in the Overworld.{*B*}
To activate the End Portal, you'll need to put an Eye of Ender into any End Portal Frame without one.{*B*}
Once the portal is active, jump in to it to go to The End.{*B*}{*B*}
In The End you will meet the Ender Dragon, a fierce and powerful enemy, along with many Enderman, so you will have to be well prepared for the battle before going there!{*B*}{*B*}
You'll find that there are Ender Crystals on top of eight Obsidian spikes that the Ender Dragon uses to heal itself, 
so the first step in the battle is to destroy each of these.{*B*}
The first few can be reached with arrows, but the later ones are protected by an Iron Fence cage, and you will need to build up to them.{*B*}{*B*}
While you are doing this, the Ender Dragon will be attacking you by flying at you and spitting Ender acid balls!{*B*}
If you approach the Egg Podium in the centre of the spikes, the Ender Dragon will fly down and attack you and this is where you can really do some damage to it!{*B*}
Avoid the acid breath, and target the Ender Dragon's eyes for the best results. If possible, bring some friends in to The End to help you with the battle!{*B*}{*B*}
Once you are in The End, your friends will be able to see the location of the End Portal within the Stronghold on their maps, 
so they can easily join you.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_SPRINT">
		<value>Sprint</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_WHATSNEW">
		<value>What's New</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_WHATSNEW">
		<value>{*T3*}Changes and Additions{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
- Added new items - Hardened Clay, Stained Clay, Block of Coal, Hay Bale, Activator Rail, Block of Redstone, Daylight Sensor, Dropper, Hopper, Minecart with Hopper, Minecart with TNT, Redstone Comparator, Weighted Pressure Plate, Beacon, Trapped Chest, Firework Rocket, Firework Star, Nether Star, Lead, Horse Armor, Name Tag, Horse Spawn Egg{*B*}
- Added new Mobs - Wither, Wither Skeletons, Witches, Bats, Horses, Donkeys and Mules{*B*}
- Added new terrain generation features - Witch Huts.{*B*}
- Added Beacon interface.{*B*}
- Added Horse interface.{*B*}
- Added Hopper interface.{*B*}
- Added Fireworks - Fireworks interface is accessible from the Crafting Table when you have the ingredients to craft a Firework Star or Firework Rocket.{*B*}
- Added 'Adventure Mode' - You can only break blocks with the correct tools.{*B*}
- Added lots of new sounds.{*B*}
- Mobs, items and projectiles can now pass through portals.{*B*}
- Repeaters can now be locked by powering their sides with another Repeater.{*B*}
- Zombies and Skeletons can now spawn with different weapons and armor.{*B*}
- New death messages.{*B*}
- Name mobs with a Name Tag, and rename containers to change the title when the menu is open.{*B*}
- Bonemeal no longer instantly grows everything to full size, and instead randomly grows in stages.{*B*}
- A Redstone signal describing the contents of Chests, Brewing Stands, Dispensers and Jukeboxes can be detected by placing a Redstone Comparator directly against them.{*B*}
- Dispensers can face in any direction.{*B*}
- Eating a Golden Apple gives the player extra "absorption" health  for a short period.{*B*}
- The longer you remain in an area the harder the monsters that spawn in that area will be.{*B*}
</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TITLEUPDATE">
		<value>{*ETB*}Welcome back! You may not have noticed but your Minecraft has just been updated.{*B*}{*B*}
There are lots of new features for you and friends to play with so here’s just a few highlights. Have a read and then go and have fun!{*B*}{*B*}
{*T1*}New Items{*ETB*} - Hardened Clay, Stained Clay, Block of Coal, Hay Bale, Activator Rail, Block of Redstone, Daylight Sensor, Dropper, Hopper, Minecart with Hopper, Minecart with TNT, Redstone Comparator, Weighted Pressure Plate, Beacon, Trapped Chest, Firework Rocket, Firework Star, Nether Star, Lead, Horse Armor, Name Tag, Horse Spawn Egg{*B*}{*B*}
{*T1*}New Mobs{*ETB*} - Wither, Wither Skeletons, Witches, Bats, Horses, Donkeys and Mules{*B*}{*B*}
{*T1*}New Features{*ETB*} -  Tame and ride a horse, craft fireworks and put on a show, name animals and monsters with a Name Tag, create more advanced Redstone circuits, and new Host Options to help control what guests to your world can do!{*B*}{*B*}
{*T1*}New Tutorial World{*ETB*} – Learn how to use the old and new features in the Tutorial World. See if you can find all the secret Music Discs hidden in the world!{*B*}{*B*}
    </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_HORSES">
		<value>Horses</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_HORSES">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : HORSES{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Horses and Donkeys are found mainly in open plains. Mules are the offspring of a Donkey and a Horse, but are infertile themselves.{*B*}
All adult Horses, Donkeys and Mules can be ridden. However only Horses can be armored, and only Mules and Donkeys may be equipped with saddlebags for transporting items.{*B*}{*B*}
Horses, Donkeys and Mules must be tamed before they can be used. A horse is tamed by attempting to ride it, and managing to stay on the horse while it attempts to throw the rider off.{*B*}
When Love Hearts appear around the horse,  it is tame, and will no longer attempt to throw the player off. To steer a horse, the player must equip the horse with a Saddle.{*B*}{*B*}
Saddles can be bought from villagers or found inside Chests hidden in the world.{*B*}
Tame Donkeys and Mules can be given saddlebags by attaching a Chest. These saddlebags can then be accessed whilst riding or sneaking.{*B*}{*B*}
Horses and Donkeys (but not Mules) can be bred like other animals using Golden Apples or Golden Carrots.{*B*}
Foals will grow into adult horses over time, although feeding them Wheat or Hay will speed this up.{*B*}
	</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_BEACONS">
		<value>Beacons</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_BEACONS">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : BEACONS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Active Beacons project a bright beam of light into the sky and grant powers to nearby players.{*B*}
They are crafted with Glass, Obsidian and Nether Stars, which can be obtained by defeating the Wither.{*B*}{*B*}
Beacons must be placed so that they are in sunlight during the day. Beacons must be placed on Pyramids of Iron, Gold, Emerald or Diamond.{*B*}
The material the Beacon is placed on has no effect on the power of the Beacon.{*B*}{*B*}
In the Beacon menu you can select one primary power for your Beacon. The more tiers your pyramid has the more powers you will have to choose from.{*B*}
A Beacon on a pyramid with at least four tiers also gives the option of either the Regeneration secondary power or a stronger primary power.{*B*}{*B*}
To set the powers of your Beacon you must sacrifice an Emerald, Diamond, Gold or Iron Ingot in the payment slot.{*B*}
Once set, the powers will emanate from the Beacon indefinitely.{*B*}
	</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_FIREWORKS">
		<value>Fireworks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_FIREWORKS">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : FIREWORKS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Fireworks are decorative items that can be launched by hand or from Dispensers. They are crafted using Paper, Gunpowder and optionally a number of Firework Stars.{*B*}
The colors, fade, shape, size, and effects (such as trails and twinkle) of Firework Stars can be customized by including additional ingredients when crafting.{*B*}{*B*}
To craft a Firework place Gunpowder and Paper in the 3x3 crafting grid that is shown above your inventory.{*B*}
You can optionally place multiple Firework Stars in the crafting grid to add them to the Firework.{*B*}
Filling more slots in the crafting grid with Gunpowder will increase the height at which all the Firework Stars will explode.{*B*}{*B*}
You can then take the crafted Firework out of the output slot.{*B*}{*B*}
Firework Stars can be crafted by placing Gunpowder and Dye into the crafting grid.{*B*}
 - The Dye will set the color of the explosion of the Firework Star.{*B*}
 - The shape of the Firework Star is set by adding either a Fire Charge, Gold Nugget, Feather or Mob Head.{*B*}
 - A trail or a twinkle can be added using Diamonds or Glowstone Dust.{*B*}{*B*}
After a Firework Star has been crafted, you can set the fade color of the Firework Star by crafting it with Dye.
	</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_HOPPERS">
		<value>Hoppers</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_HOPPERS">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : HOPPERS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Hoppers are used to insert or remove items from containers, and to automatically pick up items thrown into them.{*B*}
They can affect Brewing Stands, Chests, Dispensers, Droppers, Minecarts with Chests, Minecarts with Hoppers, as well as other Hoppers.{*B*}{*B*}
Hoppers will continuously attempt to suck items out of a suitable container placed above them. They will also attempt to insert stored items into an output container.{*B*}
If a Hopper is powered by Redstone it will become inactive and stop both sucking and inserting items.{*B*}{*B*}
A Hopper points in the direction it tries to output items. To make a Hopper point to a particular block, place the Hopper against that block whilst sneaking.{*B*}
	</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MENU_DROPPERS">
		<value>Droppers</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_DROPPERS">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : DROPPERS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
When powered by Redstone, Droppers will drop a single random item contained within them onto the ground. Use {*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to open the Dropper and then you can load the Dropper with items from your inventory.{*B*}
If the Dropper is facing a Chest or another type of Container, the item will be placed into that instead. Long chains of Droppers can be constructed to transport items over a distance, but for this to work they will have to be alternately powered on and off.
	</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SWORD">
		<value>Deals more damage than by hand.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SHOVEL">
		<value>Used to dig dirt, grass, sand, gravel and snow faster than by hand. Shovels are required to dig snowballs.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PICKAXE">
		<value>Required to mine stone-related blocks and ore.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HATCHET">
		<value>Used to chop wood-related blocks faster than by hand.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HOE">
		<value>Used to till dirt and grass blocks to prepare for crops.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DOOR_WOOD">
		<value>Wooden doors are activated by using, hitting them or with Redstone.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DOOR_IRON">
		<value>Iron doors can only be opened by Redstone, buttons or switches.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HELMET">
		<value>NOT USED</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHESTPLATE">
		<value>NOT USED</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEGGINGS">
		<value>NOT USED</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOOTS">
		<value>NOT USED</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HELMET_LEATHER">
		<value>Gives the user 1 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHESTPLATE_LEATHER">
		<value>Gives the user 3 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEGGINGS_LEATHER">
		<value>Gives the user 2 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOOTS_LEATHER">
		<value>Gives the user 1 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HELMET_CHAIN">
		<value>Gives the user 2 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHESTPLATE_CHAIN">
		<value>Gives the user 5 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEGGINGS_CHAIN">
		<value>Gives the user 4 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOOTS_CHAIN">
		<value>Gives the user 1 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HELMET_IRON">
		<value>Gives the user 2 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHESTPLATE_IRON">
		<value>Gives the user 6 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEGGINGS_IRON">
		<value>Gives the user 5 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOOTS_IRON">
		<value>Gives the user 2 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HELMET_GOLD">
		<value>Gives the user 2 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHESTPLATE_GOLD">
		<value>Gives the user 5 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEGGINGS_GOLD">
		<value>Gives the user 3 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOOTS_GOLD">
		<value>Gives the user 1 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HELMET_DIAMOND">
		<value>Gives the user 3 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHESTPLATE_DIAMOND">
		<value>Gives the user 8 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEGGINGS_DIAMOND">
		<value>Gives the user 6 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOOTS_DIAMOND">
		<value>Gives the user 3 Armor when worn.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_INGOT">
		<value>A shiny ingot which can be used to craft tools made from this material. Created by smelting ore in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BLOCK">
		<value>Allows ingots, gems, or dyes to be crafted into placeable blocks. Can be used as an expensive building block or compact storage of the ore.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PRESSUREPLATE">
		<value>Used to send an electrical charge when stepped on by a player, an animal, or a monster. Wooden Pressure Plates can also be activated by dropping something on them.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STAIRS">
		<value>Used for compact staircases.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SLAB">
		<value>Used for making long staircases. Two slabs placed on top of each other will create a normal-sized double slab block.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HALFSLAB">
		<value>Used for making long staircases. Two slabs placed on top of each other will create a normal-sized double slab block.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_TORCH">
		<value>Used to create light. Torches also melt snow and ice.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WOODENPLANKS">
		<value>Used as a building material and can be crafted into many things. Can be crafted from any form of wood.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SANDSTONE">
		<value>Used as a building material. Is not influenced by gravity like normal Sand.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STRUCTBLOCK">
		<value>Used as a building material.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STICK">
		<value>Used to craft torches, arrows, signs, ladders, fences and as handles for tools and weapons.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BED">
		<value>Used to forward time from any time at night to morning if all the players in the world are in bed, and changes the spawn point of the player. 
The colors of the bed are always the same, regardless of the colors of wool used.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CRAFTINGTABLE">
		<value>Allows you to craft a more varied selection of items than the normal crafting.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FURNACE">
		<value>Allows you to smelt ore, create charcoal and glass, and cook fish and porkchops.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHEST">
		<value>Stores blocks and items inside. Place two chests side by side to create a larger chest with double the capacity.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FENCE">
		<value>Used as a barrier that cannot be jumped over. Counts as 1.5 blocks high for players, animals and monsters, but 1 block high for other blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LADDER">
		<value>Used to climb vertically.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_TRAPDOOR">
		<value>Activated by using, hitting them or with redstone. They function as normal doors, but are a one by one block and lay flat on the ground.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SIGN">
		<value>Shows text entered by you or other players.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GLOWSTONE">
		<value>Used to create brighter light than torches. Melts snow/ice and can be used underwater.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_TNT">
		<value>Used to cause explosions. Activated after placing by igniting with Flint and Steel item, or with an electrical charge.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOWL">
		<value>Used to hold mushroom stew. You keep the bowl when the stew has been eaten.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BUCKET">
		<value>Used to hold and transport water, lava and milk.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BUCKET_WATER">
		<value>Used to hold and transport water.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BUCKET_LAVA">
		<value>Used to hold and transport lava.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BUCKET_MILK">
		<value>Used to hold and transport milk.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FLINTANDSTEEL">
		<value>Used to create fire, ignite TNT, and open a portal once it has been built.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FISHINGROD">
		<value>Used to catch fish.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CLOCK">
		<value>Displays positions of the Sun and Moon.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_COMPASS">
		<value>Points to your start point.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MAP">
		<value>Will create an image of an area explored while held. This can be used for path-finding.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MAP_EMPTY">
		<value>When used becomes a map of the part of the world that you are in, and gets filled in as you explore.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOW">
		<value>Allows for ranged attacks by using arrows.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ARROW">
		<value>Used as ammunition for bows.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_NETHER_STAR">
		<value>Dropped by the Wither, used in crafting Beacons.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FIREWORKS">
		<value>When activated, create colorful explosions. The color, effect, shape and fade are determined by the Firework Star used when the Firework is created.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FIREWORKS_CHARGE">
		<value>Used to determine the color, effect and shape of a Firework.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_COMPARATOR">
		<value>Used in Redstone circuits to maintain, compare, or subtract signal strength, or to measure certain block states.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MINECART_TNT">
		<value>Is a type of Minecart that acts as a moving TNT block.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DAYLIGHT_DETECTOR">
		<value>Is a block that outputs a Redstone signal based on sunlight (or lack of sunlight).</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MINECART_HOPPER">
		<value>Is a special type of Minecart that functions similarly to a Hopper. It will collect items lying on tracks and from containers above it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_IRON_HORSE_ARMOR">
		<value>A special type of Armor that can be equipped to a horse. Provides 5 Armor.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GOLD_HORSE_ARMOR">
		<value>A special type of Armor that can be equipped to a horse. Provides 7 Armor.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DIAMOND_HORSE_ARMOR">
		<value>A special type of Armor that can be equipped to a horse. Provides 11 Armor.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEAD">
		<value>Used to leash mobs to the player or Fence posts.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_NAME_TAG">
		<value>Used to name mobs in the world.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BREAD">
		<value>Restores 2.5{*ICON_SHANK_01*}.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CAKE">
		<value>Restores 1{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Can be used 6 times.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_COOKIE">
		<value>Restores 1{*ICON_SHANK_01*}.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MELON_SLICE">
		<value>Restores 1{*ICON_SHANK_01*}.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MUSHROOMSTEW">
		<value>Restores 3{*ICON_SHANK_01*}.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHICKEN_RAW">
		<value>Restores 1{*ICON_SHANK_01*}, or can be cooked in a furnace. Eating this can cause you to be poisoned.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHICKEN_COOKED">
		<value>Restores 3{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Created by cooking raw chicken in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BEEF_RAW">
		<value>Restores 1.5{*ICON_SHANK_01*}, or can be cooked in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BEEF_COOKED">
		<value>Restores 4{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Created by cooking raw beef in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PORKCHOP_RAW">
		<value>Restores 1.5{*ICON_SHANK_01*}, or can be cooked in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PORKCHOP_COOKED">
		<value>Restores 4{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Created by cooking a raw porkchop in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FISH_RAW">
		<value>Restores 1{*ICON_SHANK_01*}, or can be cooked in a furnace. Can be fed to an Ocelot to tame it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FISH_COOKED">
		<value>Restores 2.5{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Created by cooking a raw fish in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_APPLE">
		<value>Restores 2{*ICON_SHANK_01*}, and can be crafted into a golden apple.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GOLDENAPPLE">
		<value>Restores 2{*ICON_SHANK_01*}, and regenerates health for 4 seconds. Crafted from an apple and gold nuggets.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ROTTEN_FLESH">
		<value>Restores 2{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Eating this can cause you to be poisoned.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SUGAR">
		<value>Used in the cake recipe, and as an ingredient for brewing potions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEVER">
		<value>Used to send an electrical charge by being turned on or off. Stays in the on or off state until pressed again.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_REDSTONETORCH">
		<value>Constantly sends an electrical charge, or can be used as a receiver/transmitter when connected to the side of a block. 
Can also be used for low-level lighting.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_REDSTONEREPEATER">
		<value>Used in Redstone circuits as repeater, a delayer, and/or a diode.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BUTTON">
		<value>Used to send an electrical charge by being pressed. Stays activated for approximately a second before shutting off again.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DISPENSER">
		<value>Used to hold and shoot out items in a random order when given a Redstone charge.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_NOTEBLOCK">
		<value>Plays a note when triggered. Hit it to change the pitch of the note. Placing this on top of different blocks will change the type of instrument.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_RAIL">
		<value>Used to guide minecarts.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_POWEREDRAIL">
		<value>When powered, accelerates minecarts that pass over it. When unpowered, causes minecarts to stop on it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DETECTORRAIL">
		<value>Functions like a Pressure Plate (sends a Redstone signal when powered) but can only be activated by a Minecart.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MINECART">
		<value>Used to transport you, an animal, or a monster along rails.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MINECARTWITHCHEST">
		<value>Used to transport goods along rails.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MINECARTWITHFURNACE">
		<value>Will move along rails and can push other minecarts when coal is put in it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOAT">
		<value>Used to travel in water more quickly than swimming.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WOOL">
		<value>Collected from sheep, and can be colored with dyes.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WOOLSTRING">
		<value>Used as a building material and can be colored with dyes. This recipe is not recommended because Wool can be easily obtained from Sheep.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_BLACK">
		<value>Used as a dye to create black wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_GREEN">
		<value>Used as a dye to create green wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_BROWN">
		<value>Used as a dye to create brown wool, as an ingredient in cookies, or to grow Cocoa Pods.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_SILVER">
		<value>Used as a dye to create silver wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_YELLOW">
		<value>Used as a dye to create yellow wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_RED">
		<value>Used as a dye to create red wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_WHITE">
		<value>Used to instantly grow crops, trees, tall grass, huge mushrooms and flowers, and can be used in dye recipes.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_PINK">
		<value>Used as a dye to create pink wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_ORANGE">
		<value>Used as a dye to create orange wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_LIME">
		<value>Used as a dye to create lime wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_GRAY">
		<value>Used as a dye to create gray wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_LIGHTGRAY">
		<value>Used as a dye to create light gray wool. 
(Note: light gray dye can also be made by combining gray dye with bone meal, letting you make four light gray dyes from every ink sac instead of three.)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_LIGHTBLUE">
		<value>Used as a dye to create light blue wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_CYAN">
		<value>Used as a dye to create cyan wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_PURPLE">
		<value>Used as a dye to create purple wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_MAGENTA">
		<value>Used as a dye to create magenta wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DYE_BLUE">
		<value>Used as dye to create Blue Wool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_JUKEBOX">
		<value>Plays Music Discs.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DIAMONDS">
		<value>Use these to create very strong tools, weapons or armor.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_JACKOLANTERN">
		<value>Used to create brighter light than torches. Melts snow/ice and can be used underwater.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PAPER">
		<value>Used to create books and maps.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOOK">
		<value>Can be used to create bookshelves or enchanted to make Enchanted Books.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BOOKSHELF">
		<value>Allows the creation of more powerful enchantments when placed around the Enchantment Table.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PICTURE">
		<value>Used as decoration.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ORE_GOLD">
		<value>Can be mined with an iron pickaxe or better, then smelted in a furnace to produce gold ingots.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ORE_IRON">
		<value>Can be mined with a stone pickaxe or better, then smelted in a furnace to produce iron ingots.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ORE_COAL">
		<value>Can be mined with a pickaxe to collect coal.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ORE_LAPIS">
		<value>Can be mined with a stone pickaxe or better to collect lapis lazuli.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ORE_DIAMOND">
		<value>Can be mined with an iron pickaxe or better to collect diamonds.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ORE_REDSTONE">
		<value>Can be mined with an iron pickaxe or better to collect redstone dust.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STONE">
		<value>Can be mined with a pickaxe to collect cobblestone.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DIRT">
		<value>Collected using a shovel. Can be used for construction.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SAPLING">
		<value>Can be planted and it will eventually grow into a tree.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BEDROCK">
		<value>This cannot be broken.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LAVA">
		<value>Sets fire to anything that touches it. Can be collected in a bucket.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SAND">
		<value>Collected using a shovel. Can be smelted into glass using the furnace. Is affected by gravity if there is no other tile underneath it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GRAVEL">
		<value>Collected using a shovel. Sometimes produces flint when dug up. Is affected by gravity if there is no other tile underneath it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LOG">
		<value>Chopped using an axe, and can be crafted into planks or used as a fuel.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GLASS">
		<value>Created in a furnace by smelting sand. Can be used for construction, but will break if you try to mine it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STONE_BRICK">
		<value>Mined from stone using a pickaxe. Can be used to construct a furnace or stone tools.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BRICK">
		<value>Baked from clay in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CLAY">
		<value>Can be baked into bricks in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CLAY_TILE">
		<value>When broken drops clay balls which can be baked into bricks in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SNOW">
		<value>A compact way to store snowballs.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_TOP_SNOW">
		<value>Can be dug with a shovel to create snowballs.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_TALL_GRASS">
		<value>Sometimes produces wheat seeds when broken.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FLOWER">
		<value>Can be crafted into a dye.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MUSHROOM">
		<value>Can be crafted with a bowl to make stew.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_OBSIDIAN">
		<value>Can only be mined with a diamond pickaxe. Is produced by the meeting of water and still lava, and is used to build a portal.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MOB_SPAWNER">
		<value>Spawns monsters into the world.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_REDSTONE_DUST">
		<value>Is placed on the ground to carry an electrical charge. When brewed with a potion it will increase the duration of the effect.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CROPS">
		<value>When fully grown, crops can be harvested to collect wheat.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FARMLAND">
		<value>Ground that has been prepared ready to plant seeds.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CACTUS">
		<value>Can be cooked in a furnace to create a green dye.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_REEDS">
		<value>Can be crafted to create sugar.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PUMPKIN">
		<value>Can be worn as a helmet or crafted with a torch to create a Jack-O-Lantern. It is also the main ingredient in Pumpkin Pie.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HELL_ROCK">
		<value>Burns forever if set alight.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HELL_SAND">
		<value>Slows the movement of anything walking over it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PORTAL">
		<value>Standing in the portal allows you to pass between the Overworld and the Nether.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_COAL">
		<value>Used as a fuel in a furnace, or crafted to make a torch.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STRING">
		<value>Collected by killing a spider, and can be crafted into a Bow or Fishing Rod, or placed on the ground to create Tripwire.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FEATHER">
		<value>Collected by killing a chicken, and can be crafted into an arrow.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SULPHUR">
		<value>Collected by killing a Creeper, and can be crafted into TNT or used as an ingredient for brewing potions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WHEAT_SEEDS">
		<value>Can be planted in farmland to grow crops. Make sure there's enough light for the seeds to grow!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WHEAT">
		<value>Harvested from crops, and can be used to craft food items.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FLINT">
		<value>Collected by digging gravel, and can be used to craft a flint and steel.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SADDLE">
		<value>When used on a pig it allows you to ride the pig. The pig can then be steered using a Carrot on a Stick.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SNOWBALL">
		<value>Collected by digging snow, and can be thrown.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEATHER">
		<value>Collected by killing a cow, and can be crafted into armor or used to make Books.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SLIMEBALL">
		<value>Collected by killing a Slime, and used as an ingredient for brewing potions or crafted to make Sticky Pistons.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_EGG">
		<value>Dropped randomly by chickens, and can be crafted into food items.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_YELLOW_DUST">
		<value>Collected by mining Glowstone, and can be crafted to make Glowstone blocks again or brewed with a potion to increase the potency of the effect.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BONE">
		<value>Collected by killing a Skeleton. Can be crafted into bone meal. Can be fed to a wolf to tame it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_RECORD">
		<value>Collected by getting a Skeleton to kill a Creeper. Can be played in a jukebox.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WATER">
		<value>Extinguishes fire and helps crops grow. Can be collected in a bucket.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LEAVES">
		<value>When broken sometimes drops a sapling which can then be replanted to grow into a tree.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MOSS_STONE">
		<value>Found in dungeons, can be used for construction and decoration.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SHEARS">
		<value>Used to obtain wool from sheep and harvest leaf blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PISTON">
		<value>When powered (using a button, a lever, a pressure plate, a redstone torch, or redstone with any one of these), a piston extends if it can and pushes blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STICKY_PISTON">
		<value>When powered (using a button, a lever, a pressure plate, a redstone torch, or redstone with any one of these), a piston extends if it can and pushes blocks. When it retracts it pulls back the block touching the extended part of the piston.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STONE_BRICK_SMOOTH">
		<value>Made from Stone blocks, and commonly found in Strongholds.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_IRON_FENCE">
		<value>Used as a barrier, similar to fences.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FENCE_GATE">
		<value>Similar to a door, but used primarily with fences.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MELON_BLOCK">
		<value>Can be crafted from Melon Slices.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_THIN_GLASS">
		<value>Transparent blocks that can be used as an alternative to Glass Blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PUMPKIN_SEEDS">
		<value>Can be planted to grow pumpkins.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MELON_SEEDS">
		<value>Can be planted to grow melons.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ENDER_PEARL">
		<value>Dropped by Enderman when they die. When thrown, the player will be teleported to the position the Ender Pearl lands at, and will lose some health.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GRASS">
		<value>A block of dirt with grass growing on top. Collected using a shovel. Can be used for construction.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SPONGE">
		<value>Can be used for construction and decoration.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WEB">
		<value>Slows movement when walking through it. Can be destroyed using shears to collect string.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STONE_SILVERFISH">
		<value>Spawns a Silverfish when destroyed. May also spawn Silverfish if nearby to another Silverfish being attacked.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_VINE">
		<value>Grows over time when placed. Can be collected using shears. Can be climbed like a ladder.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ICE">
		<value>Slippery when walked on. Turns into water if above another block when destroyed. Melts if close enough to a light source or when placed in The Nether.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DEAD_BUSH">
		<value>Can be used as decoration.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BLAZE_ROD">
		<value>Used in potion brewing, and for locating Strongholds. Dropped by Blazes who tend to be found near or in Nether Fortresses.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GHAST_TEAR">
		<value>Used in potion brewing. Dropped by Ghasts when they die.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GOLD_NUGGET">
		<value>Dropped by Zombie Pigmen when they die. Zombie Pigmen can be found in the Nether. Used as an ingredient for brewing potions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_NETHER_STALK_SEEDS">
		<value>Used in potion brewing. This can be found naturally growing in Nether Fortresses. It can also be planted on Soul Sand.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_POTION">
		<value>When used, can have various effects, depending on what it is used on.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GLASS_BOTTLE">
		<value>Can be filled with water, and used as the starting ingredient for a potion in the Brewing Stand.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SPIDER_EYE">
		<value>This is a poisonous food and brewing item. Dropped when a Spider or Cave Spider is killed by a player.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FERMENTED_SPIDER_EYE">
		<value>Used in potion brewing, mainly to create potions with a negative effect.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BLAZE_POWDER">
		<value>Used in potion brewing, or crafted with other items to make Eye of Ender or Magma Cream.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MAGMA_CREAM">
		<value>Used in potion brewing.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BREWING_STAND">
		<value>Used for making Potions and Splash Potions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CAULDRON">
		<value>Filled with water by rain or with a bucket of water, and can then be used to fill Glass Bottles with water.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_EYE_OF_ENDER">
		<value>When thrown, will show the direction to an End Portal. When twelve of these are placed in the End Portal Frames, the End Portal will be activated.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SPECKLED_MELON">
		<value>Used in potion brewing.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MYCEL">
		<value>Similar to Grass Blocks, but very good for growing mushrooms on.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WATERLILY">
		<value>Floats on water, and can be walked on.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_NETHERBRICK">
		<value>Used to build Nether Fortresses. Immune to Ghast's fireballs.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_NETHERFENCE">
		<value>Used in Nether Fortresses.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_NETHERSTALK">
		<value>Found in Nether Fortresses, and will drop Nether Wart when broken.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ENCHANTMENTTABLE">
		<value>This allows players to enchant Swords, Pickaxes, Axes, Shovels, Bows and Armor, using the player's Experience Points.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_END_PORTAL">
		<value>This can be activated using twelve Eye of Ender, and will allow the player to travel to The End dimension.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ENDPORTALFRAME">
		<value>Used to form an End Portal.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WHITESTONE">
		<value>A block type found in The End. It has a very high blast resistance, so is useful for building with.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DRAGONEGG">
		<value>This block is created by the defeat of the Dragon in The End.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_EXP_BOTTLE">
		<value>When thrown, it drops Experience Orbs which increase your experience points when collected.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FIREBALL">
		<value>Useful for setting things on fire, or for indiscriminately starting fires when fired from a Dispenser.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ITEMFRAME">
		<value>These are similar to a display case, and will display the item or block placed in it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MONSTER_SPAWNER">
		<value>When thrown can spawn a creature of the type indicated.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WOODSLAB">
		<value>Used for making long staircases. Two slabs placed on top of each other will create a normal-sized double slab block.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STONESLAB">
		<value>Used for making long staircases. Two slabs placed on top of each other will create a normal-sized double slab block.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ITEM_NETHERBRICK">
		<value>Created by smelting Netherrack in a furnace. Can be crafted into Nether Brick blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_REDSTONE_LIGHT">
		<value>When powered they emit light.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_COCOA">
		<value>Can be farmed to collect Cocoa Beans.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SKULL">
		<value>Mob Heads can be placed as a decoration, or worn as a mask in the helmet slot.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_COMMAND_BLOCK">
		<value>Used to execute commands.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BEACON">
		<value>Projects a beam of light into the sky and can provide Status Effects to nearby players.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHEST_TRAP">
		<value>Stores blocks and items inside. Place two chest side by side to create a larger chest with double capacity. The trapped chest also creates a Redstone charge when opened.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WEIGHTED_PLATE_LIGHT">
		<value>Provides a Redstone charge. The charge will be stronger if more items are on the plate.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WEIGHTED_PLATE_HEAVY">
		<value>Provides a Redstone charge. The charge will be stronger if more items are on the plate. Requires more weight than the light plate.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_REDSTONE_BLOCK">
		<value>Used as a redstone power source. Can be crafted back into Redstone.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HOPPER">
		<value>Used to catch items or to transfer items into and out of containers.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ACTIVATOR_RAIL">
		<value>A type of rail that can enable or disable Minecarts with Hoppers and trigger Minecarts with TNT.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DROPPER">
		<value>Used to hold and drop items, or push items into another container, when given a Redstone charge.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STAINED_CLAY">
		<value>Colorful blocks crafted by dyeing Hardened clay.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HAY">
		<value>Can be fed to Horses, Donkeys or Mules to heal up to 10 Hearts. Speeds up the growth of foals.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HARDENED_CLAY">
		<value>Created by smelting Clay in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STAINED_GLASS">
		<value>Crafted from glass and a dye.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_STAINED_GLASS_PANE">
		<value>Crafted from Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_COAL_BLOCK">
		<value>A compact way of storing Coal. Can be used as fuel in a Furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SQUID">
		<value>Squid</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SQUID">
		<value>Drops ink sacs when killed.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_COW">
		<value>Cow</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_COW">
		<value>Drops leather when killed. Can also be milked with a bucket.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SHEEP">
		<value>Sheep</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SHEEP">
		<value>Drops wool when sheared (if it has not already been sheared). Can be dyed to make its wool a different color.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHICKEN">
		<value>Chicken</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CHICKEN">
		<value>Drops feathers when killed, and also randomly lays eggs.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PIG">
		<value>Pig</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PIG">
		<value>Drops porkchops when killed. Can be ridden by using a saddle.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WOLF">
		<value>Wolf</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WOLF">
		<value>Docile until attacked, when they will attack you back. Can be tamed using bones which causes the wolf to follow you around and attack anything that attacks you.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREEPER">
		<value>Creeper</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CREEPER">
		<value>Explodes if you get too close!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SKELETON">
		<value>Skeleton</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SKELETON">
		<value>Fires arrows at you. Drops arrows when killed.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SPIDER">
		<value>Spider</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SPIDER">
		<value>Attacks you when you are close to it. Can climb walls. Drops string when killed.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ZOMBIE">
		<value>Zombie</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ZOMBIE">
		<value>Attacks you when you are close to it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PIGZOMBIE">
		<value>Zombie Pigman</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PIGZOMBIE">
		<value>Initially docile, but will attack in groups if you attack one.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GHAST">
		<value>Ghast</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_GHAST">
		<value>Fires flaming balls at you that explode on contact.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIME">
		<value>Slime</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SLIME">
		<value>Split into smaller Slimes when damaged.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENDERMAN">
		<value>Enderman</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ENDERMAN">
		<value>Will attack you if you look at it. Can also move blocks around.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SILVERFISH">
		<value>Silverfish</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SILVERFISH">
		<value>Attracts nearby hidden Silverfish when attacked. Hides in stone blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CAVE_SPIDER">
		<value>Cave Spider</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CAVE_SPIDER">
		<value>Has a venomous bite.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MUSHROOM_COW">
		<value>Mooshroom</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MUSHROOM_COW">
		<value>Makes mushroom stew when used with a bowl. Drops mushrooms and becomes a normal cow when sheared.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SNOWMAN">
		<value>Snow Golem</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_SNOWMAN">
		<value>The Snow Golem can be created by players using snow blocks and a pumpkin. They will throw snowballs at their creators enemies.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENDERDRAGON">
		<value>Ender Dragon</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ENDERDRAGON">
		<value>This is a large black dragon found in The End.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_BLAZE">
		<value>Blaze</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BLAZE">
		<value>These are enemies found in the Nether, mostly inside Nether Fortresses. They will drop Blaze Rods when killed.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LAVA_SLIME">
		<value>Magma Cube</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_LAVA_SLIME">
		<value>These can be found in The Nether. Similar to Slimes, they will break up into smaller versions when killed.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_VILLAGER">
		<value>Villager</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_OZELOT">
		<value>Ocelot</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_OZELOT">
		<value>These can be found in Jungles. They can be tamed by feeding them Raw Fish. You will need to let the Ocelot approach you though, since any sudden movements will scare it away.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_IRONGOLEM">
		<value>Iron Golem</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_IRONGOLEM">
		<value>Appear in Villages to protect them, and can be created using Iron Blocks and Pumpkins.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_BAT">
		<value>Bat</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BAT">
		<value>These flying creatures are found in caverns or other large enclosed spaces.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WITCH">
		<value>Witch</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WITCH">
		<value>These enemies can be found in swamps and attack you by throwing Potions. They drop Potions when killed.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HORSE">
		<value>Horse</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_HORSE">
		<value>These animals can be tamed and can then be ridden.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DONKEY">
		<value>Donkey</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_DONKEY">
		<value>These animals can be tamed and can then be ridden. They can have a chest attached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MULE">
		<value>Mule</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_MULE">
		<value>Born when a Horse and a Donkey breed. These animals can be tamed and can then be ridden and carry chests.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ZOMBIE_HORSE">
		<value>Zombie Horse</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SKELETON_HORSE">
		<value>Skeleton Horse</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WITHER">
		<value>Wither</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_WITHER">
		<value>These are crafted from Wither Skulls and Soul Sand. They fire exploding skulls at you.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_EXPLODANIM">
		<value>Explosives Animator</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_CONCEPTART">
		<value>Concept Artist</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_CRUNCHER">
		<value>Number Crunching and Statistics</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_BULLYCOORD">
		<value>Bully Coordinator</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_ORIGINALDESIGN">
		<value>Original Design and Code by</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_PMPROD">
		<value>Project Manager/Producer</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_RESTOFMOJANG">
		<value>Rest of Mojang Office</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_LEADPC">
		<value>Lead Game Programmer Minecraft PC</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_CODENINJA">
		<value>Ninja Coder</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_CEO">
		<value>CEO</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_WCW">
		<value>White Collar Worker</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_CUSTOMERSUPPORT">
		<value>Customer Support</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_OFFICEDJ">
		<value>Office DJ</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_DESPROG">
		<value>Designer/Programmer Minecraft - Pocket Edition</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_DEVELOPER">
		<value>Developer</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_CHIEFARCHITECT">
		<value>Chief Architect</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_ARTDEVELOPER">
		<value>Art Developer</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_GAMECRAFTER">
		<value>Game Crafter</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_DOF">
		<value>Director of Fun</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_MUSICANDSOUNDS">
		<value>Music and Sounds</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_PROGRAMMING">
		<value>Programming</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_ART">
		<value>Art</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_QA">
		<value>QA</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_EXECPRODUCER">
		<value>Executive Producer</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_LEADPRODUCER">
		<value>Lead Producer</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_PRODUCER">
		<value>Producer</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_TESTLEAD">
		<value>Test Lead</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_LEADTESTER">
		<value>Lead Tester</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_DESIGNTEAM">
		<value>Design Team</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_DEVELOPMENTTEAM">
		<value>Development Team</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_RELEASEMANAGEMENT">
		<value>Release Management</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_XBLADIRECTOR">
		<value>Director, XBLA Publishing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_BIZDEV">
		<value>Business Development</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_PORTFOLIODIRECTOR">
		<value>Portfolio Director</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_PRODUCTMANAGER">
		<value>Product Manager</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_MARKETING">
		<value>Marketing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_COMMUNITYMANAGER">
		<value> Community Manager</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_EUROPELOC">
		<value>Europe Localization Team</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_REDMONDLOC">
		<value>Redmond Localization Team</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_ASIALOC">
		<value>Asia Localization Team</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_USERRESEARCH">
		<value>User Research Team</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_MGSCENTRAL">
		<value>MGS Central Teams</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_MILESTONEACCEPT">
		<value>Milestone Acceptance Tester</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_SPECIALTHANKS">
		<value>Special Thanks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_TESTMANAGER">
		<value>Test Manager</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_SRTESTLEAD">
		<value>Senior Test Lead</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_SDET">
		<value>SDET</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_PROJECT">
		<value>Project STE</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_ADDITIONALSTE">
		<value>Additional STE</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_TESTASSOCIATES">
		<value>Test Associates</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_JON_KAGSTROM">
		<value>Jon Kågström</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_TOBIAS_MOLLSTAM">
		<value>Tobias Möllstam</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS_RISE_LUGO">
		<value>Risë Lugo</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SWORD_WOOD">
		<value>Wooden Sword</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SWORD_STONE">
		<value>Stone Sword</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SWORD_IRON">
		<value>Iron Sword</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SWORD_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Sword</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SWORD_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Sword</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SHOVEL_WOOD">
		<value>Wooden Shovel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SHOVEL_STONE">
		<value>Stone Shovel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SHOVEL_IRON">
		<value>Iron Shovel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SHOVEL_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Shovel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SHOVEL_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Shovel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PICKAXE_WOOD">
		<value>Wooden Pickaxe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PICKAXE_STONE">
		<value>Stone Pickaxe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PICKAXE_IRON">
		<value>Iron Pickaxe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PICKAXE_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Pickaxe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PICKAXE_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Pickaxe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HATCHET_WOOD">
		<value>Wooden Axe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HATCHET_STONE">
		<value>Stone Axe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HATCHET_IRON">
		<value>Iron Axe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HATCHET_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Axe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HATCHET_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Axe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HOE_WOOD">
		<value>Wooden Hoe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HOE_STONE">
		<value>Stone Hoe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HOE_IRON">
		<value>Iron Hoe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HOE_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Hoe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HOE_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Hoe</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DOOR_WOOD">
		<value>Wooden Door</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DOOR_IRON">
		<value>Iron Door</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HELMET_CHAIN">
		<value>Chain Helmet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CHESTPLATE_CHAIN">
		<value>Chain Chestplate</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_LEGGINGS_CHAIN">
		<value>Chain Leggings</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BOOTS_CHAIN">
		<value>Chain Boots</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HELMET_CLOTH">
		<value>Leather Cap</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HELMET_IRON">
		<value>Iron Helmet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HELMET_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Helmet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_HELMET_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Helmet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CHESTPLATE_CLOTH">
		<value>Leather Tunic</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CHESTPLATE_IRON">
		<value>Iron Chestplate</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CHESTPLATE_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Chestplate</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CHESTPLATE_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Chestplate</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_LEGGINGS_CLOTH">
		<value>Leather Pants</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_LEGGINGS_IRON">
		<value>Iron Leggings</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_LEGGINGS_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Leggings</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_LEGGINGS_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Leggings</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BOOTS_CLOTH">
		<value>Leather Boots</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BOOTS_IRON">
		<value>Iron Boots</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BOOTS_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Boots</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BOOTS_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Boots</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_INGOT_IRON">
		<value>Iron Ingot</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_INGOT_GOLD">
		<value>Gold Ingot</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BUCKET">
		<value>Bucket</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BUCKET_WATER">
		<value>Water Bucket</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BUCKET_LAVA">
		<value>Lava Bucket</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FLINT_AND_STEEL">
		<value>Flint and Steel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_APPLE">
		<value>Apple</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BOW">
		<value>Bow</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_ARROW">
		<value>Arrow</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_COAL">
		<value>Coal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CHARCOAL">
		<value>Charcoal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_STICK">
		<value>Stick</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BOWL">
		<value>Bowl</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MUSHROOM_STEW">
		<value>Mushroom Stew</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_STRING">
		<value>String</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FEATHER">
		<value>Feather</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SULPHUR">
		<value>Gunpowder</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_WHEAT_SEEDS">
		<value>Wheat Seeds</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_WHEAT">
		<value>Wheat</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BREAD">
		<value>Bread</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FLINT">
		<value>Flint</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PORKCHOP_RAW">
		<value>Raw Porkchop</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PORKCHOP_COOKED">
		<value>Cooked Porkchop</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PAINTING">
		<value>Painting</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_APPLE_GOLD">
		<value>Golden Apple</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SIGN">
		<value>Sign</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MINECART">
		<value>Minecart</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SADDLE">
		<value>Saddle</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_REDSTONE">
		<value>Redstone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SNOWBALL">
		<value>Snowball</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BOAT">
		<value>Boat</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_LEATHER">
		<value>Leather</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BUCKET_MILK">
		<value>Milk Bucket</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BRICK">
		<value>Brick</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CLAY">
		<value>Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_REEDS">
		<value>Sugar Canes</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PAPER">
		<value>Paper</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BOOK">
		<value>Book</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SLIMEBALL">
		<value>Slimeball</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MINECART_CHEST">
		<value>Minecart with Chest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MINECART_FURNACE">
		<value>Minecart with Furnace</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_EGG">
		<value>Egg</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_COMPASS">
		<value>Compass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FISHING_ROD">
		<value>Fishing Rod</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CLOCK">
		<value>Clock</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_YELLOW_DUST">
		<value>Glowstone Dust</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FISH_RAW">
		<value>Raw Fish</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FISH_COOKED">
		<value>Cooked Fish</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER">
		<value>Dye Powder</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_BLACK">
		<value>Ink Sac</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_RED">
		<value>Rose Red</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_GREEN">
		<value>Cactus Green</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_BROWN">
		<value>Cocoa Beans</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_BLUE">
		<value>Lapis Lazuli</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_PURPLE">
		<value>Purple Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_CYAN">
		<value>Cyan Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_SILVER">
		<value>Light Gray Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_GRAY">
		<value>Gray Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_PINK">
		<value>Pink Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_LIME">
		<value>Lime Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_YELLOW">
		<value>Dandelion Yellow</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_LIGHT_BLUE">
		<value>Light Blue Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_MAGENTA">
		<value>Magenta Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_ORANGE">
		<value>Orange Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DYE_POWDER_WHITE">
		<value>Bone Meal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BONE">
		<value>Bone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SUGAR">
		<value>Sugar</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CAKE">
		<value>Cake</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BED">
		<value>Bed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DIODE">
		<value>Redstone Repeater</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_COOKIE">
		<value>Cookie</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MAP">
		<value>Map</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MAP_EMPTY">
		<value>Empty Map</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_01">
		<value>Music Disc - "13"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_02">
		<value>Music Disc - "cat"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_03">
		<value>Music Disc - "blocks"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_04">
		<value>Music Disc - "chirp"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_05">
		<value>Music Disc - "far"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_06">
		<value>Music Disc - "mall"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_07">
		<value>Music Disc - "mellohi"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_08">
		<value>Music Disc - "stal"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_09">
		<value>Music Disc - "strad"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_10">
		<value>Music Disc - "ward"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_11">
		<value>Music Disc - "11"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_RECORD_12">
		<value>Music Disc - "where are we now"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SHEARS">
		<value>Shears</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PUMPKIN_SEEDS">
		<value>Pumpkin Seeds</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MELON_SEEDS">
		<value>Melon Seeds</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CHICKEN_RAW">
		<value>Raw Chicken</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CHICKEN_COOKED">
		<value>Cooked Chicken</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BEEF_RAW">
		<value>Raw Beef</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BEEF_COOKED">
		<value>Steak</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_ROTTEN_FLESH">
		<value>Rotten Flesh</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_ENDER_PEARL">
		<value>Ender Pearl</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MELON_SLICE">
		<value>Melon Slice</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BLAZE_ROD">
		<value>Blaze Rod</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_GHAST_TEAR">
		<value>Ghast Tear</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_GOLD_NUGGET">
		<value>Gold Nugget</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_NETHER_STALK_SEEDS">
		<value>Nether Wart</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_POTION">
		<value>{*splash*}{*prefix*}Potion {*postfix*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_GLASS_BOTTLE">
		<value>Glass Bottle</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_WATER_BOTTLE">
		<value>Water Bottle</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SPIDER_EYE">
		<value>Spider Eye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FERMENTED_SPIDER_EYE">
		<value>Fermented Spider Eye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BLAZE_POWDER">
		<value>Blaze Powder</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MAGMA_CREAM">
		<value>Magma Cream</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_BREWING_STAND">
		<value>Brewing Stand</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CAULDRON">
		<value>Cauldron</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_EYE_OF_ENDER">
		<value>Eye of Ender</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SPECKLED_MELON">
		<value>Glistering Melon</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_EXP_BOTTLE">
		<value>Bottle o' Enchanting</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FIREBALL">
		<value>Fire Charge</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FIREBALLCHARCOAL">
		<value>Fire Charge (Charcoal)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FIREBALLCOAL">
		<value>Fire Charge (Coal)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_ITEMFRAME">
		<value>Item Frame</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MONSTER_SPAWNER">
		<value>Spawn {*CREATURE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_NETHERBRICK">
		<value>Nether Brick</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SKULL">
		<value>Skull</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SKULL_SKELETON">
		<value>Skeleton Skull</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SKULL_WITHER">
		<value>Wither Skeleton Skull</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SKULL_ZOMBIE">
		<value>Zombie Head</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SKULL_CHARACTER">
		<value>Head</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SKULL_PLAYER">
		<value>%s's Head</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_SKULL_CREEPER">
		<value>Creeper Head</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NETHER_STAR">
		<value>Nether Star</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS">
		<value>Firework Rocket</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE">
		<value>Firework Star</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_COMPARATOR">
		<value>Redstone Comparator</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MINECART_TNT">
		<value>Minecart with TNT</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_MINECART_HOPPER">
		<value>Minecart with Hopper</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_IRON_HORSE_ARMOR">
		<value>Iron Horse Armor</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_GOLD_HORSE_ARMOR">
		<value>Gold Horse Armor</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_DIAMOND_HORSE_ARMOR">
		<value>Diamond Horse Armor</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_LEAD">
		<value>Lead</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_NAME_TAG">
		<value>Name Tag</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE">
		<value>Stone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_GRASS">
		<value>Grass Block</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DIRT">
		<value>Dirt</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE_BRICK">
		<value>Cobblestone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_OAKWOOD_PLANKS">
		<value>Oak Wood Planks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SPRUCEWOOD_PLANKS">
		<value>Spruce Wood Planks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BIRCHWOOD_PLANKS">
		<value>Birch Wood Planks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_JUNGLE_PLANKS">
		<value>Jungle Wood Planks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_PLANKS">
		<value>Wood Planks (any type)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SAPLING">
		<value>Sapling</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SAPLING_OAK">
		<value>Oak Sapling</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SAPLING_SPRUCE">
		<value>Spruce Sapling</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SAPLING_BIRCH">
		<value>Birch Sapling</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SAPLING_JUNGLE">
		<value>Jungle Tree Sapling</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BEDROCK">
		<value>Bedrock</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_WATER">
		<value>Water</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LAVA">
		<value>Lava</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SAND">
		<value>Sand</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SANDSTONE">
		<value>Sandstone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_GRAVEL">
		<value>Gravel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ORE_GOLD">
		<value>Gold Ore</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ORE_IRON">
		<value>Iron Ore</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ORE_COAL">
		<value>Coal Ore</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LOG">
		<value>Wood</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LOG_OAK">
		<value>Oak Wood</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LOG_SPRUCE">
		<value>Spruce Wood</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LOG_BIRCH">
		<value>Birch Wood</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LOG_JUNGLE">
		<value>Jungle Wood</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_OAK">
		<value>Oak</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SPRUCE">
		<value>Spruce</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BIRCH">
		<value>Birch</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LEAVES">
		<value>Leaves</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LEAVES_OAK">
		<value>Oak Leaves</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LEAVES_SPRUCE">
		<value>Spruce Leaves</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LEAVES_BIRCH">
		<value>Birch Leaves</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LEAVES_JUNGLE">
		<value>Jungle Leaves</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SPONGE">
		<value>Sponge</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_GLASS">
		<value>Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH">
		<value>Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_BLACK">
		<value>Black Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_RED">
		<value>Red Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_GREEN">
		<value>Green Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_BROWN">
		<value>Brown Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_BLUE">
		<value>Blue Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_PURPLE">
		<value>Purple Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_CYAN">
		<value>Cyan Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_SILVER">
		<value>Light Gray Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_GRAY">
		<value>Gray Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_PINK">
		<value>Pink Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_LIME">
		<value>Lime Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_YELLOW">
		<value>Yellow Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_LIGHT_BLUE">
		<value>Light Blue Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_MAGENTA">
		<value>Magenta Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_ORANGE">
		<value>Orange Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLOTH_WHITE">
		<value>White Wool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_FLOWER">
		<value>Flower</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ROSE">
		<value>Rose</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_MUSHROOM">
		<value>Mushroom</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BLOCK_GOLD">
		<value>Block of Gold</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BLOCK_GOLD">
		<value>A compact way of storing Gold.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BLOCK_IRON">
		<value>A compact way of storing Iron.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BLOCK_IRON">
		<value>Block of Iron</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB">
		<value>Stone Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_STONE">
		<value>Stone Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_SAND">
		<value>Sandstone Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_WOOD">
		<value>Oak Wood Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_COBBLE">
		<value>Cobblestone Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_BRICK">
		<value>Bricks Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_SMOOTHBRICK">
		<value>Stone Bricks Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_OAK">
		<value>Oak Wood Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_SPRUCE">
		<value>Spruce Wood Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_BIRCH">
		<value>Birch Wood Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_JUNGLE">
		<value>Jungle Wood Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_NETHERBRICK">
		<value>Nether Brick Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BRICK">
		<value>Bricks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_TNT">
		<value>TNT</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BOOKSHELF">
		<value>Bookshelf</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE_MOSS">
		<value>Moss Stone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_OBSIDIAN">
		<value>Obsidian</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_TORCH">
		<value>Torch</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_TORCHCOAL">
		<value>Torch (Coal)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_TORCHCHARCOAL">
		<value>Torch (Charcoal)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_FIRE">
		<value>Fire</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_MOB_SPAWNER">
		<value>Monster Spawner</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_WOOD">
		<value>Oak Wood Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CHEST">
		<value>Chest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_REDSTONE_DUST">
		<value>Redstone Dust</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ORE_DIAMOND">
		<value>Diamond Ore</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BLOCK_DIAMOND">
		<value>Block of Diamond</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BLOCK_DIAMOND">
		<value>A compact way of storing Diamonds.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_WORKBENCH">
		<value>Crafting Table</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CROPS">
		<value>Crops</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_FARMLAND">
		<value>Farmland</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_FURNACE">
		<value>Furnace</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SIGN">
		<value>Sign</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DOOR_WOOD">
		<value>Wooden Door</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LADDER">
		<value>Ladder</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_RAIL">
		<value>Rail</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_GOLDEN_RAIL">
		<value>Powered Rail</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DETECTOR_RAIL">
		<value>Detector Rail</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_STONE">
		<value>Stone Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LEVER">
		<value>Lever</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_PRESSURE_PLATE">
		<value>Pressure Plate</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DOOR_IRON">
		<value>Iron Door</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ORE_REDSTONE">
		<value>Redstone Ore</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_NOT_GATE">
		<value>Redstone Torch</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BUTTON">
		<value>Button</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SNOW">
		<value>Snow</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ICE">
		<value>Ice</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CACTUS">
		<value>Cactus</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CLAY">
		<value>Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_REEDS">
		<value>Sugar Cane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_JUKEBOX">
		<value>Jukebox</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_FENCE">
		<value>Fence</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_PUMPKIN">
		<value>Pumpkin</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LIT_PUMPKIN">
		<value>Jack-O-Lantern</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_HELL_ROCK">
		<value>Netherrack</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_HELL_SAND">
		<value>Soul Sand</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LIGHT_GEM">
		<value>Glowstone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_PORTAL">
		<value>Portal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ORE_LAPIS">
		<value>Lapis Lazuli Ore</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BLOCK_LAPIS">
		<value>Lapis Lazuli Block</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_BLOCK_LAPIS">
		<value>A compact way of storing Lapis Lazuli.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DISPENSER">
		<value>Dispenser</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_MUSIC_BLOCK">
		<value>Note Block</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CAKE">
		<value>Cake</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BED">
		<value>Bed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_WEB">
		<value>Web</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_TALL_GRASS">
		<value>Tall Grass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DEAD_BUSH">
		<value>Dead Bush</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DIODE">
		<value>Diode</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_LOCKED_CHEST">
		<value>Locked Chest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_TRAPDOOR">
		<value>Trapdoor</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ANY_WOOL">
		<value>Wool (any color)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_PISTON_BASE">
		<value>Piston</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_PISTON_STICK_BASE">
		<value>Sticky Piston</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_MONSTER_STONE_EGG">
		<value>Silverfish Block</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE_BRICK_SMOOTH">
		<value>Stone Bricks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE_BRICK_SMOOTH_MOSSY">
		<value>Mossy Stone Bricks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE_BRICK_SMOOTH_CRACKED">
		<value>Cracked Stone Bricks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE_BRICK_SMOOTH_CHISELED">
		<value>Chiseled Stone Bricks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_HUGE_MUSHROOM_1">
		<value>Mushroom</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_HUGE_MUSHROOM_2">
		<value>Mushroom</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_IRON_FENCE">
		<value>Iron Bars</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_THIN_GLASS">
		<value>Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_MELON">
		<value>Melon</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_PUMPKIN_STEM">
		<value>Pumpkin Stem</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_MELON_STEM">
		<value>Melon Stem</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_VINE">
		<value>Vines</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_FENCE_GATE">
		<value>Fence Gate</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_BRICKS">
		<value>Brick Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_STONE_BRICKS_SMOOTH">
		<value>Stone Brick Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE_SILVERFISH">
		<value>Silverfish Stone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE_SILVERFISH_COBBLESTONE">
		<value>Silverfish Cobblestone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONE_SILVERFISH_STONE_BRICK">
		<value>Silverfish Stone Brick</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_MYCEL">
		<value>Mycelium</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_WATERLILY">
		<value>Lily Pad</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_NETHERBRICK">
		<value>Nether Brick</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_NETHERFENCE">
		<value>Nether Brick Fence</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_NETHERBRICK">
		<value>Nether Brick Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_NETHERSTALK">
		<value>Nether Wart</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ENCHANTMENTTABLE">
		<value>Enchantment Table</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BREWINGSTAND">
		<value>Brewing Stand</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CAULDRON">
		<value>Cauldron</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_END_PORTAL">
		<value>End Portal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ENDPORTALFRAME">
		<value>End Portal Frame</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_WHITESTONE">
		<value>End Stone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DRAGONEGG">
		<value>Dragon Egg</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SHRUB">
		<value>Shrub</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_FERN">
		<value>Fern</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_SANDSTONE">
		<value>Sandstone Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_SPRUCEWOOD">
		<value>Spruce Wood Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_BIRCHWOOD">
		<value>Birch Wood Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_JUNGLEWOOD">
		<value>Jungle Wood Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_REDSTONE_LIGHT">
		<value>Redstone Lamp</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_COCOA">
		<value>Cocoa</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SKULL">
		<value>Skull</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_COMMAND_BLOCK">
		<value>Command Block</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BEACON">
		<value>Beacon</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CHEST_TRAP">
		<value>Trapped Chest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_WEIGHTED_PLATE_LIGHT">
		<value>Weighted Pressure Plate (Light)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_WEIGHTED_PLATE_HEAVY">
		<value>Weighted Pressure Plate (Heavy)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_COMPARATOR">
		<value>Redstone Comparator</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DAYLIGHT_DETECTOR">
		<value>Daylight Sensor</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_REDSTONE_BLOCK">
		<value>Block of Redstone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_HOPPER">
		<value>Hopper</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ACTIVATOR_RAIL">
		<value>Activator Rail</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DROPPER">
		<value>Dropper</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY">
		<value>Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_HAY">
		<value>Hay Bale</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_HARDENED_CLAY">
		<value>Hardened Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_COAL">
		<value>Block of Coal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_BLACK">
		<value>Black Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_RED">
		<value>Red Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_GREEN">
		<value>Green Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_BROWN">
		<value>Brown Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_BLUE">
		<value>Blue Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_PURPLE">
		<value>Purple Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_CYAN">
		<value>Cyan Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_SILVER">
		<value>Light Gray Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_GRAY">
		<value>Gray Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_PINK">
		<value>Pink Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_LIME">
		<value>Lime Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_YELLOW">
		<value>Yellow Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_LIGHT_BLUE">
		<value>Light Blue Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_MAGENTA">
		<value>Magenta Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_ORANGE">
		<value>Orange Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_CLAY_WHITE">
		<value>White Stained Clay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS">
		<value>Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_BLACK">
		<value>Black Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_RED">
		<value>Red Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_GREEN">
		<value>Green Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_BROWN">
		<value>Brown Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_BLUE">
		<value>Blue Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PURPLE">
		<value>Purple Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_CYAN">
		<value>Cyan Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_SILVER">
		<value>Light Gray Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_GRAY">
		<value>Gray Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PINK">
		<value>Pink Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_LIME">
		<value>Lime Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_YELLOW">
		<value>Yellow Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_LIGHT_BLUE">
		<value>Light Blue Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_MAGENTA">
		<value>Magenta Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_ORANGE">
		<value>Orange Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_WHITE">
		<value>White Stained Glass</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE">
		<value>Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_BLACK">
		<value>Black Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_RED">
		<value>Red Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_GREEN">
		<value>Green Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_BROWN">
		<value>Brown Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_BLUE">
		<value>Blue Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_PURPLE">
		<value>Purple Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_CYAN">
		<value>Cyan Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_SILVER">
		<value>Light Gray Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_GRAY">
		<value>Gray Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_PINK">
		<value>Pink Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_LIME">
		<value>Lime Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_YELLOW">
		<value>Yellow Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_LIGHT_BLUE">
		<value>Light Blue Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_MAGENTA">
		<value>Magenta Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_ORANGE">
		<value>Orange Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAINED_GLASS_PANE_WHITE">
		<value>White Stained Glass Pane</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_TYPE_0">
		<value>Small Ball</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_TYPE_1">
		<value>Large Ball</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_TYPE_2">
		<value>Star-shaped</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_TYPE_3">
		<value>Creeper-shaped</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_TYPE_4">
		<value>Burst</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_TYPE">
		<value>Unknown Shape</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_BLACK">
		<value>Black</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_RED">
		<value>Red</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_GREEN">
		<value>Green</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_BROWN">
		<value>Brown</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_BLUE">
		<value>Blue</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_PURPLE">
		<value>Purple</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_CYAN">
		<value>Cyan</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_SILVER">
		<value>Light Gray</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_GRAY">
		<value>Gray</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_PINK">
		<value>Pink</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_LIME">
		<value>Lime</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_YELLOW">
		<value>Yellow</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_LIGHT_BLUE">
		<value>Light Blue</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_MAGENTA">
		<value>Magenta</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_ORANGE">
		<value>Orange</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_WHITE">
		<value>White</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_CUSTOM">
		<value>Custom</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_FADE_TO">
		<value>Fade to</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_FLICKER">
		<value>Twinkle</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIREWORKS_CHARGE_TRAIL">
		<value>Trail</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_FIREWORKS_FLIGHT">
		<value>Flight Duration:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CURRENT_LAYOUT">
		<value>Current Controls</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_LAYOUT">
		<value>Layout</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_MOVE">
		<value>Move/Sprint</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_LOOK">
		<value>Look</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_PAUSE">
		<value>Pause</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_JUMP">
		<value>Jump</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_JUMPFLY">
		<value>Jump/Fly Up</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_INVENTORY">
		<value>Inventory</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_HELDITEM">
		<value>Cycle Held Item</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_ACTION">
		<value>Action</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_USE">
		<value>Use</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_CRAFTING">
		<value>Crafting</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_DROP">
		<value>Drop</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_SNEAK">
		<value>Sneak</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_SNEAKFLY">
		<value>Sneak/Fly Down</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_THIRDPERSON">
		<value>Change Camera Mode</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_PLAYERS">
		<value>Players/Invite</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_DPAD">
		<value>Movement (When Flying)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_SCHEME0">
		<value>Layout 1</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_SCHEME1">
		<value>Layout 2</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS_SCHEME2">
		<value>Layout 3</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_A">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonA.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_B">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonB.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_X">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonX.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_Y">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonY.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_LEFT_STICK">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonLeftStick.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_RIGHT_STICK">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonRightStick.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_LEFT_TRIGGER">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonLeftTrigger.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_RIGHT_TRIGGER">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonRightTrigger.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_LEFT_BUMPER">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonLeftBumper.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_RIGHT_BUMPER">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonRightBumper.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_BACK">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonBack.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_START">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonStart.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_RIGHT_THUMBSTICK">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonRS.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_LEFT_THUMBSTICK">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonLS.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_DPAD_R">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonDpadR.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_DPAD_L">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonDpadL.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_DPAD_U">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonDpadU.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLLER_DPAD_D">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\X360ControllerIcons\ButtonDpadD.png" align="middle" height="30" width="30"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ICON_SHANK_01">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\Icon_Shank.png" align="middle" height="22" width="22"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ICON_SHANK_03">
		<value><![CDATA[&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\Icon_Shank.png" align="middle" height="22" width="22"/&gt;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\Icon_Shank.png" align="middle" height="22" width="22"/&gt;&lt;img src="{*IMAGEROOT*}Graphics\Icon_Shank.png" align="middle" height="22" width="22"/&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_PRESS_A_TO_CONTINUE">
		<value>{*B*}Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_START_TUTORIAL">
		<value>{*B*}Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to start the tutorial.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you think you are ready to play on your own.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_OVERVIEW">
		<value>Minecraft is a game about placing blocks to build anything you can imagine.  
At night monsters come out, make sure to build a shelter before that happens.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_LOOK">
		<value>Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_LOOK*} to look up, down and around.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_MOVE">
		<value>Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*} to move around.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_SPRINT">
		<value>To sprint, push{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*} forward twice quickly. While you hold{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*} forward, the character will continue to sprint unless they run out of sprint time or food.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_JUMP">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_JUMP*} to jump.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_MINE">
		<value>Hold{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_ACTION*} to mine and chop using your hand or whatever you are holding. You may need to craft a tool to mine some blocks...</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CHOP_WOOD">
		<value>Hold{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_ACTION*} to chop down 4 blocks of wood (tree trunks).{*B*}When a block breaks you can pick it up by standing near to the floating item that appears, causing it to appear in your inventory.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFTING">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_CRAFTING*} to open the crafting interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_INVENTORY">
		<value>As you collect and craft more items, your inventory will fill up.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_INVENTORY*} to open the inventory.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FOOD_BAR_DEPLETE">
		<value>As you move around, mine and attack, you will deplete your food bar{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Sprinting and sprint jumping use a lot more food than walking and jumping normally.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FOOD_BAR_HEAL">
		<value>If you lose some health, but have a food bar with 9 or more{*ICON_SHANK_01*} in it, your health will automatically replenish. Eating food will replenish your food bar.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FOOD_BAR_FEED">
		<value>With a food item in your hand, hold{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to eat it and replenish your food bar. You cannot eat if your food bar is full.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FOOD_BAR_EAT_STEAK">
		<value>Your food bar is low, and you have lost some health. Eat the steak in your inventory to replenish your food bar and start healing.{*ICON*}364{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_PLANKS">
		<value>The wood that you have collected can be crafted into planks. Open the crafting interface to craft them.{*PlanksIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_CRAFTING_TABLE">
		<value>A lot of crafting can involve multiple steps. Now that you have some planks there are more items that you can craft. Create a crafting table.{*CraftingTableIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_STICKS">
		<value>To make collecting blocks faster you can build tools designed for the job. Some tools have a handle made of sticks. Craft some sticks now.{*SticksIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_SCROLL">
		<value>Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_LEFT_SCROLL*} and{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_RIGHT_SCROLL*} to change the current held item.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_USE">
		<value>Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to use items, interact with objects and place some items. Items that have been placed can be picked up again by mining them with the right tool.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_PLACE_WORKBENCH">
		<value>With the crafting table selected, point the crosshair where you want it and use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to place a crafting table.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_OPEN_WORKBENCH">
		<value>Point the crosshair at the crafting table and press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to open it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_WOODEN_SHOVEL">
		<value>A shovel helps dig soft blocks, like dirt and snow, faster. As you collect more materials you can craft tools that work faster and last longer. Create a wooden shovel.{*WoodenShovelIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_WOODEN_HATCHET">
		<value>An axe helps chop wood and wooden tiles, faster. As you collect more materials you can craft tools that work faster and last longer. Create a wooden axe.{*WoodenHatchetIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_WOODEN_PICKAXE">
		<value>A pickaxe helps dig hard blocks, like stone and ore, faster. As you collect more materials you can craft tools that work faster and last longer, and allow you to mine harder materials. Create a wooden pickaxe.{*WoodenPickaxeIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_OPEN_CONTAINER">
		<value>Open the container</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_NIGHT_DANGER">
		<value>Night time can approach quickly, and it is dangerous to be outside unprepared. You can craft armor and weapons, but it is sensible to have a safe shelter.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_NEARBY_SHELTER">
		<value>Nearby there is an abandoned Miner's shelter that you can complete to be safe overnight.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_COLLECT_RESOURCES">
		<value>You will need to collect the resources to complete the shelter. Walls and roof can be made of any tile type, but you will want to create a door, some windows and lighting.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_MINE_STONE">
		<value>Use your pickaxe to mine some stone blocks. Stone blocks will produce cobblestone when mined. If you collect 8 cobblestone blocks you can build a furnace. You may need to dig through some dirt to reach the stone, so use your shovel for this.{*StoneIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_FURNACE">
		<value>You have collected enough cobblestone to build a furnace. Use your crafting table to create one.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_PLACE_AND_OPEN_FURNACE">
		<value>Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to place the furnace in the world, and then open it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_CHARCOAL">
		<value>Use the furnace to create some charcoal. If you are waiting for it to finish how about using the time to collect more materials to finish the shelter?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_GLASS">
		<value>Use the furnace to create some glass. If you are waiting for it to finish how about using the time to collect more materials to finish the shelter?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_WOODEN_DOOR">
		<value>A good shelter will have a door so that you can easily go in and out without having to mine and replace the walls. Craft a wooden door now.{*WoodenDoorIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_PLACE_DOOR">
		<value>Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to place the door. You can use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to open and close a wooden door in the world.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATE_TORCH">
		<value>It can get very dark at night, so you will want some lighting inside your shelter so that you can see. Craft a torch now from sticks and charcoal using the crafting interface.{*TorchIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BASIC_COMPLETE">
		<value>You have completed the first part of the tutorial.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_BASIC_COMPLETE">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue with the tutorial.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you think you are ready to play on your own.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_INV_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is your inventory. It shows items available for use in your hand, and all the other items that you are carrying. Your armor is also shown here.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_INV_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know how to use the inventory.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_INV_PICK_UP">
		<value>Use{*CONTROLLER_MENU_NAVIGATE*} to move the pointer. Use{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to pick an item under the pointer.
If there is more than one item here this will pick them all up, or you can use{*CONTROLLER_VK_X*} to pick up just half of them.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_INV_MOVE">
		<value>Move this item with the pointer over another space in the inventory and place it down using{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*}.
With multiple items on the pointer, use{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to place them all, or{*CONTROLLER_VK_X*} to place just one.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_INV_DROP">
		<value>If you move the pointer outside the edge of the interface with an item on the pointer, you can drop the item.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_INV_INFO">
		<value>If you want more information about an item, move the pointer over the item and press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MENU_PAGEDOWN*} .</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_INV_EXIT">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} now to exit the inventory.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_INV_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is the creative mode inventory. It shows items available for use in your hand, and all the other items that you can choose from.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_CREATIVE_INV_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know how to use the creative mode inventory.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_INV_PICK_UP">
		<value>Use{*CONTROLLER_MENU_NAVIGATE*} to move the pointer.
When on the item list, use{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to pick an item under the pointer, and use{*CONTROLLER_VK_Y*} to pick up a full stack of that item.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_INV_MOVE">
		<value>The pointer will automatically move over a space in the use row. You can place it down using{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*}. Once you have placed the item, the pointer will return to the item list where you can select another item.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_INV_DROP">
		<value>If you move the pointer outside the edge of the interface with an item on the pointer, you can drop the item into the world. To clear all items in the quick select bar, press{*CONTROLLER_VK_X*}.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_INV_NAV">
		<value>Scroll through the Group Type tabs at the top using{*CONTROLLER_VK_LB*} and{*CONTROLLER_VK_RB*} to select the group type of the item you wish to pickup.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_INV_INFO">
		<value>If you want more information about an item, move the pointer over the item and press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MENU_PAGEDOWN*} .</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_INV_EXIT">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} now to exit the creative mode inventory.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is the crafting interface. This interface allows you to combine the items you've collected to make new items.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_CRAFT_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know how to craft.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_PRESS_X_TO_TOGGLE_DESCRIPTION">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_X*} to show the item description.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_PRESS_X_TO_TOGGLE_INGREDIENTS">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_X*} to show the ingredients required to make the current item.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_PRESS_X_TO_TOGGLE_INVENTORY">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_X*} to show the inventory again.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_NAV">
		<value>Scroll through the Group Type tabs at the top using{*CONTROLLER_VK_LB*} and{*CONTROLLER_VK_RB*} to select the group type of the item you wish to craft, then use{*CONTROLLER_MENU_NAVIGATE*} to select the item to craft.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_CREATE">
		<value>The crafting area shows the items you require in order to craft the new item. Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to craft the item and place it in your inventory.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_CRAFT_TABLE">
		<value>You can craft a larger selection of items using a crafting table. Crafting on a table works in the same way as basic crafting, but you have a larger crafting area allowing more combinations of ingredients.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_INVENTORY">
		<value>The bottom right part of the crafting interface shows your inventory. This area can also show a description of the currently selected item, and the ingredients required to craft it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_DESCRIPTION">
		<value>The description of the currently selected item is now displayed. The description can give you an idea of what the item can be used for.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_INGREDIENTS">
		<value>The list of ingredients required to craft the selected item are now displayed.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_CREATE_PLANKS">
		<value>The wood that you have collected can be crafted into planks. Select the planks icon and press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to create them.{*PlanksIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_EXIT_AND_PLACE_TABLE">
		<value>Now you have built a crafting table you should place it in the world to enable you to build a larger selection of items.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} now to exit the crafting interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_SELECT_TOOLS">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_LB*} and{*CONTROLLER_VK_RB*} to change to the group type of the items you wish to craft. Select the tools group.{*ToolsIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_SELECT_STRUCTURES">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_LB*} and{*CONTROLLER_VK_RB*} to change to the group type of the items you wish to craft. Select the structures group.{*StructuresIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_SELECT_WOODEN_SHOVEL">
		<value>Use{*CONTROLLER_MENU_NAVIGATE*} to change to the item you wish to craft. Some items have multiple versions depending on the materials used. Select the wooden shovel.{*WoodenShovelIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_SELECT_CRAFTING_TABLE">
		<value>A lot of crafting can involve multiple steps. Now that you have some planks there are more items that you can craft. Use{*CONTROLLER_MENU_NAVIGATE*} to change to the item you wish to craft. Select the crafting table.{*CraftingTableIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_TOOLS_BUILT">
		<value>With the tools you have built you are off to a great start, and are able to collect a variety of different materials more efficiently.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} now to exit the crafting interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_CREATE_FURNACE">
		<value>Some items can not be created using the crafting table, but require a furnace. Craft a furnace now.{*FurnaceIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CRAFT_EXIT_AND_PLACE_FURNACE">
		<value>Place the furnace you have crafted in the world. You will want to put this inside your shelter.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} now to exit the crafting interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FURNACE_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is the furnace interface. A furnace allows you to change items by firing them. For example, you can turn iron ore into iron ingots in the furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_FURNACE_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know how to use a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FURNACE_METHOD">
		<value>You need to put some fuel into the bottom slot of the furnace, and the item to be changed in the top slot. The furnace will then fire up and start working, putting the result in the right-hand slot.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FURNACE_FUELS">
		<value>Many wooden items can be used as fuels, but not everything burns for the same time. You may also discover other items in the world that can be used as a fuel.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FURNACE_INGREDIENTS">
		<value>When your items have been fired, you can move them from the output area into your inventory. You should experiment with different ingredients to see what you can make.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FURNACE_CREATE_CHARCOAL">
		<value>If you use wood as the ingredient then you can make charcoal. Put some fuel in the furnace and wood in the ingredient slot. It can take some time for the furnace to create the charcoal, so feel free to do something else and come back to check the progress.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FURNACE_CHARCOAL_USES">
		<value>Charcoal can be used as a fuel, as well as being crafted into a torch with a stick.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FURNACE_CREATE_GLASS">
		<value>Placing sand in the ingredient slot allows you to make glass. Create some glass blocks to use as windows in your shelter.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is the brewing interface. You can use this to create potions that have a variety of different effects.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_BREWING_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know how to use the brewing stand.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_MENU_METHOD">
		<value>You brew potions by placing an ingredient in the top slot, and a potion or water bottle in the bottom slots (up to 3 can be brewed at one time). Once a valid combination is entered the brewing process will start and create the potion after a short time.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_MENU_BASIC_INGREDIENTS">
		<value>All potions start with a Water Bottle. Most potions are created by first using a Nether Wart to make an Awkward Potion, and will require at least one more ingredient to make the final potion.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_MENU_EXTENDED_INGREDIENTS">
		<value>Once you have a potion you can modify its effects. Adding Redstone Dust increases the duration of its effect and adding Glowstone Dust can make its effect more powerful.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_MENU_EXTENDED_INGREDIENTS_2">
		<value>Adding Fermented Spider Eye corrupts the potion and can turn it into a potion with the opposite effect, and adding Gunpowder turns the potion into a Splash Potion which can be thrown to apply its affect to a nearby area.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_MENU_CREATE_FIRE_POTION">
		<value>Create a Potion of Fire Resistance by first adding Nether Wart to a Water Bottle, and then adding Magma Cream.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_MENU_EXIT">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} now to exit the brewing interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>In this area there is a Brewing Stand, a Cauldron and a chest full of items for brewing.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_BREWING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about brewing and potions.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about brewing and potions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_GET_GLASS_BOTTLE">
		<value>The first step in brewing a potion is to create a Water Bottle. Take a Glass Bottle from the chest.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_FILL_GLASS_BOTTLE">
		<value>You can fill a glass bottle from a Cauldron that has water in it, or from a block of water. Fill your glass bottle now by pointing at a water source and pressing{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*}.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_FILL_CAULDRON">
		<value>If a cauldron becomes empty, you can refill it with a Water Bucket.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_CREATE_FIRE_POTION">
		<value>Use the Brewing Stand to create a Potion of Fire Resistance. You will need a Water Bottle, Nether Wart and Magma Cream.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_USE_POTION">
		<value>With a potion in your hand, hold{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to use it. For a normal potion you will drink it and apply the effect to yourself, and for a Splash potion you will throw it and apply the effect to creatures near where it hits. 
Splash potions can be created by adding gunpowder to normal potions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_DRINK_FIRE_POTION">
		<value>Use your Potion of Fire Resistance on yourself.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREWING_USE_EFFECTS">
		<value>Now that you are resistant to fire and lava, you should see if there are places you can get to that you couldn't before.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is the enchanting interface which you can use to add enchantments to weapons, armor and some tools.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_ENCHANTING_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about the enchanting interface.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about the enchanting interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_MENU_START">
		<value>To enchant an item, first place it in the enchanting slot. Weapons, armor and some tools can be enchanted to add special effects such as improved damage resistance or increasing the number of items produced when mining a block.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_MENU_ENCHANTMENTS">
		<value>When an item is placed in the enchanting slot, the buttons on the right will change to show a selection of random enchantments.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_MENU_COST">
		<value>The number on the button represents the cost in experience levels to apply that enchantment to the item. If you do not have a high enough level the button will be disabled.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_MENU_ENCHANT">
		<value>Select an enchantment and press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to enchant the item. This will decrease your experience level by the cost of the enchantment.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_MENU_BETTER_ENCHANTMENTS">
		<value>Although the enchantments are all random, some of the better enchantments are only available when you have a high experience level and have lots of bookcases around the Enchantment Table to increase its power.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>In this area there is an Enchantment Table and some other items to help you learn about enchanting.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_ENCHANTING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about enchanting.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about enchanting.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_SUMMARY">
		<value>Using an Enchantment Table allows you to add special effects such as increasing the number of items produced when mining a block, or improved damage resistance for weapons, armor and some tools.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_BOOKCASES">
		<value>Placing bookcases around the Enchantment Table increases its power and allows access to higher level enchantments.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_EXPERIENCE">
		<value>Enchanting items costs Experience Levels, which can be built up by collecting Experience Orbs which are produced by killing monsters and animals, mining ores, breeding animals, fishing and smelting/cooking some things in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_BOTTLE_O_ENCHANTING">
		<value>You can also build experience levels using a Bottle O' Enchanting, which, when thrown, creates Experience Orbs around where it lands. These orbs can then be collected.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_USE_CHESTS">
		<value>In the chests in this area you can find some enchanted items, Bottles O' Enchanting, and some items that have yet to be enchanted for you to experiment with at the Enchantment Table.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_MINECART_OVERVIEW">
		<value>You are now riding in a minecart. To exit the minecart, point the cursor at it and press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} .{*MinecartIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_MINECART_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about minecarts.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about minecarts.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_MINECART_RAILS">
		<value>A minecart runs on rails. You can also craft a powered minecart with a furnace and a minecart with a chest in it.{*RailIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_MINECART_POWERED_RAILS">
		<value>You can also craft powered rails, which take power from redstone torches and circuits to accelerate the cart. These can be connected to switches, levers and pressure plates to make complex systems.{*PoweredRailIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BOAT_OVERVIEW">
		<value>You are now sailing a boat. To exit the boat, point the cursor at it and press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} .{*BoatIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_BOAT_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about boats.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about boats.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BOAT_STEER">
		<value>A boat allows you to travel quicker over water. You can steer it using{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*} and{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_LOOK*}.{*BoatIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FISHING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>You are now using a fishing rod. Press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to use it.{*FishingRodIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_FISHING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about fishing.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about fishing.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FISHING_CAST">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} to cast your line and start fishing. Press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} again to reel in the fishing line.{*FishingRodIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FISHING_FISH">
		<value>If you wait until the float sinks below the surface of the water before reeling in you can catch a fish. Fish can be eaten raw, or cooked by a furnace, to restore health.{*FishIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FISHING_USES">
		<value>As with many other tools a fishing rod has a fixed number of uses. Those uses are not limited to catching fish though. You should experiment with it to see what else can be caught or activated...{*FishingRodIcon*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BED_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is a bed. Press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} while pointing at it at night to sleep through the night and awake in the morning.{*ICON*}355{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_BED_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about beds.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about beds.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BED_PLACEMENT">
		<value>A bed should be placed in a safe, well-lit place so that monsters do not wake you in the middle of the night. Once you have used a bed, if you die you will respawn at that bed.
{*ICON*}355{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BED_MULTIPLAYER">
		<value>If there are other players in your game, everyone must be in a bed at the same time to be able to sleep.
{*ICON*}355{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_REDSTONE_OVERVIEW">
		<value>In this area there are some simple Redstone and Piston circuits, and a chest with more items to extend these circuits.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_REDSTONE_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about Redstone circuits and Pistons.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about Redstone circuits and Pistons.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_REDSTONE_POWER_SOURCES">
		<value>Levers, Buttons, Pressure Plates and Redstone Torches can all provide power to circuits, either by directly attaching them to the item you want to activate or by connecting them with Redstone dust.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_REDSTONE_POWER_SOURCES_POSITION">
		<value>The position and direction that you place a power source can change how it affects the surrounding blocks. For example a Redstone torch on the side of a block can be turned off if the block is powered by another source.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_REDSTONE_DUST">
		<value>Redstone dust is collected by mining redstone ore with a pickaxe made of Iron, Diamond or Gold. You can use it to carry power up to 15 blocks, and it can travel up or down one block in height.
{*ICON*}331{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_REDSTONE_REPEATER">
		<value>Redstone repeaters can be used to extend the distance that the power is carried, or put a delay in a circuit.
{*ICON*}356{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_PISTONS">
		<value>When powered, a Piston will extend, pushing up to 12 blocks. When they retract, Sticky Pistons can pull back one block of most types.
{*ICON*}33{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRY_IT">
		<value>In the chest in this area there are some components for making circuits with pistons. Try using or completing the circuits in this area, or put together your own. There are more examples outside the tutorial area.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PORTAL_OVERVIEW">
		<value>In this area there is a Portal to the Nether!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_PORTAL_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about Portals and The Nether.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about Portals and The Nether.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BUILD_PORTAL">
		<value>Portals are created by placing Obsidian blocks into a frame four blocks wide and five blocks tall. The corner blocks are not required.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ACTIVATE_PORTAL">
		<value>To activate a Nether Portal, set fire to the Obsidian blocks inside the frame with a Flint and Steel. Portals can be deactivated if their frame is broken, an explosion happens nearby or a liquid flows through them.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_USE_PORTAL">
		<value>To use a Nether Portal, stand inside it. Your screen will go purple and a sound will play. After a few seconds you will be transported to another dimension.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_NETHER">
		<value>The Nether can be a dangerous place, full of lava, but can be useful to collect Netherrack which burns forever when lit, and Glowstone which produces light.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_NETHER_FAST_TRAVEL">
		<value>The Nether world can be used to fast-travel in the Overworld - traveling one block distance in the Nether is equivalent to traveling 3 blocks in the Overworld.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_CREATIVE_OVERVIEW">
		<value>You are now in Creative mode.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_CREATIVE_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about Creative mode.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about Creative mode.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_MODE">
		<value>When in Creative mode you have in infinite number of all available items and blocks, you can destroy blocks with one click without a tool, you are invulnerable and you can fly.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_OPEN_CREATIVE_INVENTORY">
		<value>Press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_CRAFTING*} to open the creative inventory interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_EXIT">
		<value>Make your way to the opposite side of this hole to continue.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_CREATIVE_COMPLETE">
		<value>You have now completed the Creative mode tutorial.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_FARMING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>In this area a farm has been set up. Farming enables you to create a renewable source of food and other items.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_FARMING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about farming.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about farming.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_SEEDS">
		<value>Wheat, Pumpkins and Melons are grown from seeds. Wheat seeds are collected by breaking Tall Grass or harvesting wheat, and Pumpkin and Melon seeds are crafted from Pumpkins and Melons respectively.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_FARMLAND">
		<value>Before planting seeds the dirt blocks need to be turned into Farmland by using a Hoe. A nearby source of water will help keep the Farmland hydrated and make the crops grow faster, as will keeping the area lit.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_WHEAT">
		<value>Wheat goes through several stages when growing, and is ready to be harvested when it appears darker.{*ICON*}59:7{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_PUMPKIN_AND_MELON">
		<value>Pumpkins and Melons also need a block next to where you planted the seed for the fruit to grow once the stem has fully grown.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_SUGARCANE">
		<value>Sugarcane must be planted on a Grass, Dirt or Sand block that is right next to water block. Chopping a Sugarcane block will also drop all blocks that are above it.{*ICON*}83{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_CACTUS">
		<value>Cacti must be planted on Sand, and will grow up to three blocks high. Like Sugarcane, destroying the lowest block will also allow you to collect the blocks that are above it.{*ICON*}81{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_MUSHROOM">
		<value>Mushrooms should be planted in a dimly lit area, and will spread to nearby dimly lit blocks.{*ICON*}39{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_BONEMEAL">
		<value>Bonemeal can be used to grow crops to their fully grown state, or grow Mushrooms into Huge Mushrooms.{*ICON*}351:15{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_COMPLETE">
		<value>You have now completed the farming tutorial.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_BREEDING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>In this area animals have been penned in. You can breed animals to produce baby versions of themselves.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_BREEDING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about animals and breeding.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about animals and breeding.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREEDING_FEED">
		<value>To get the animals to breed, you will need to feed them with the right food to get them to go into 'Love Mode'.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREEDING_FEED_FOOD">
		<value>Feed Wheat to a cow, mooshroom or sheep, Carrots to pigs, Wheat Seeds or Nether Wart to a chicken, or any kind of meat to a wolf, and they'll start looking for another animal of the same species near them that is also in Love Mode.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREEDING_BABY">
		<value>When two animals of the same species meet, and both are in Love Mode, they will kiss for a few seconds, and then a baby animal will appear. The baby animal will follow their parents for a while before growing into a full sized animal itself.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREEDING_DELAY">
		<value>After being in Love Mode, an animal will not be able to enter it again for about five minutes.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREEDING_FOLLOW">
		<value>Some animals will follow you if you are holding their food in your hand. This makes it easier to group animals together to breed them.{*ICON*}296{*/ICON*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREEDING_WOLF_TAMING">
		<value>Wild wolves can be tamed by giving them bones. Once tamed Love Hearts will appear around them. Tamed wolves will follow the player and defend them if they haven't been commanded to sit.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREEDING_COMPLETE">
		<value>You have now completed the animal and breeding tutorial.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_GOLEM_OVERVIEW">
		<value>In this area are some pumpkins and blocks to make a Snow Golem and an Iron Golem.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_GOLEM_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about Golems.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about Golems.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_GOLEM_PUMPKIN">
		<value>Golems are created by placing a pumpkin on top of a stack of blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_GOLEM_SNOW">
		<value>Snow Golems are created with two Snow Blocks, one of top of the other, with a pumpkin on top. Snow Golems throw snowballs at your enemies.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_GOLEM_IRON">
		<value>Iron Golems are created with four Iron Blocks in the pattern shown, with a pumpkin on top of the middle block. Iron Golems attack your enemies.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_GOLEM_IRON_VILLAGE">
		<value>Iron Golems also appear naturally to protect villages, and will attack you if you attack any villagers.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_CONSTRAINT_TUTORIAL_AREA">
		<value>You cannot leave this area until you have completed the tutorial.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_DIGGER_ITEM_SHOVEL">
		<value>Different tools are better for different materials. You should use a shovel to mine soft materials like earth and sand.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_DIGGER_ITEM_HATCHET">
		<value>Different tools are better for different materials. You should use an axe to chop tree trunks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_DIGGER_ITEM_PICKAXE">
		<value>Different tools are better for different materials. You should use a pickaxe to mine stone and ore. You may need to make your pickaxe from better materials to get resources from some blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_ATTACK_WITH_TOOL">
		<value>Certain tools are better for attacking enemies. Consider using a sword to attack.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_HOLD_TO_MINE">
		<value>Hint: Hold {*CONTROLLER_ACTION_ACTION*}to mine and chop using your hand or whatever you are holding. You may need to craft a tool to mine some blocks...</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_TOOL_DAMAGED">
		<value>The tool you are using has become damaged. Every time you use a tool it becomes damaged, and will eventually break. The colored bar below the item in your inventory shows the current damage state.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_SWIM_UP">
		<value>Hold{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_JUMP*} to swim up.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_MINECART">
		<value>In this area there is a minecart on a track. To enter the minecart, point the cursor at it and press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*}. Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} on the button to make the minecart move.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_BOAT">
		<value>In the chest beside the river there is a boat. To use the boat, point the cursor at water and press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*}. Use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} while pointing at the boat to enter it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_FISHING">
		<value>In the chest beside the pond there is a fishing rod. Take the fishing rod from the chest and select it as the current item in your hand to use it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_PISTON_SELF_REPAIRING_BRIDGE">
		<value>This more advanced piston mechanism creates a self-repairing bridge! Push the button to activate, then investigate how the components interact to learn more.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_INV_DROP">
		<value>If you move the pointer outside of the interface while carrying an item, you can drop that item.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HINT_CRAFT_NO_INGREDIENTS">
		<value>You do not have all the ingredients required to make this item. The box on the bottom left shows the ingredients required to craft this.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_COMPLETED">
		<value>Congratulations, you have completed the tutorial. Time in the game is now passing normally, and you don't have long until night time and the monsters come out! Finish your shelter!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_COMPLETED_EXPLORE">
		<value>{*EXIT_PICTURE*}	  When you are ready to explore further, there is a stairway in this area near the Miner's shelter that leads to a small castle.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_REMINDER">
		<value>Reminder: </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_HTML_EXIT_PICTURE">
		<value><![CDATA[&lt;div align="center"&gt;&lt;img src="Graphics\TutorialExitScreenshot.png"/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_NEW_FEATURES_CHOICE">
		<value>New features have been added to the game in the latest version, including new areas in the tutorial world.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_NEW_FEATURES_CHOICE">
		<value>{*B*}Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to play through the tutorial as normal.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} to skip the main tutorial.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_FEATURES_IN_THIS_AREA">
		<value>In this area you will find areas setup to help you learn about fishing, boats, pistons and redstone.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_FEATURES_OUTSIDE_THIS_AREA">
		<value>Outside of this area you will find examples of buildings, farming, minecarts and tracks, enchanting, brewing, trading, smithing and more!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FOOD_BAR_OVERVIEW">
		<value>Your food bar has depleted to a level where you will no longer heal.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_FOOD_BAR_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about the food bar and eating food.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about the food bar and eating food.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is the horse inventory interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_HORSE_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue.
{*B*}Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know how to use the horse inventory.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_MENU_LAYOUT">
		<value>The horse inventory allows you to transfer, or equip items to your Horse, Donkey or Mule.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_MENU_EQUIPMENT">
		<value>Saddle your Horse by placing a Saddle in the saddle slot. Horses can be given armor by placing Horse Armor in the armor slot.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_MENU_SADDLEBAGS">
		<value>You can also transfer items between your own inventory and the saddlebags strapped to Donkeys and Mules in this menu.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_OVERVIEW">
		<value>You have found a Horse.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_DONKEY_OVERVIEW">
		<value>You have found a Donkey.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_MULE_OVERVIEW">
		<value>You have found a Mule.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_HORSE_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about Horses, Donkeys and Mules.
{*B*}Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about Horses, Donkeys and Mules.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_INTRO">
		<value>Horses and Donkeys are found mainly in open plains. Mules can be bred from a Donkey and a Horse, but are infertile themselves.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_PURPOSE">
		<value>All adult Horses, Donkeys and Mules can be ridden. However only Horses can be armored, and only Mules and Donkeys may be equipped with saddlebags for transporting items.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_TAMING">
		<value>Horses, Donkeys and Mules must be tamed before they can be used. A horse is tamed by attempting to ride it, and managing to stay on the horse while it attempts to throw the rider off. </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_TAMING2">
		<value>When tamed Love Hearts will appear around them and they will no longer buck the player off.  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_RIDE">
		<value>Try to ride this horse now. Use {*CONTROLLER_ACTION_USE*} with no items or tools in your hand to mount it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_SADDLES">
		<value>To steer a horse they must then be equipped with a saddle, which can be bought from villagers or found inside chests hidden in the world.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_SADDLEBAGS">
		<value>Tame Donkeys and Mules can be given saddlebags by attaching a chest. These bags can be accessed whilst riding or when sneaking.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_BREEDING">
		<value>Horses and Donkeys (but not Mules) can be bred like other animals using Golden Apples or Golden Carrots. Foals will grow into adult horses over time, although feeding them wheat or hay will speed this up.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HORSE_AREA">
		<value>You can try to tame the Horses and Donkeys here, and there are Saddles, Horse Armor and other useful items for Horses in chests around here too.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BEACON_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is the Beacon interface, which you can use to choose powers for your Beacon to grant.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_BEACON_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know how to use the Beacon interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BEACON_MENU_PRIMARY_POWERS">
		<value>In the Beacon menu you can select 1 primary power for your Beacon. The more tiers your pyramid has the more powers you will have to choose from.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BEACON_MENU_SECONDARY_POWER">
		<value>A Beacon on a pyramid with at least 4 tiers grants an additional option of either the Regeneration secondary power or a stronger primary power.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BEACON_MENU_ACTIVATION">
		<value>To set the powers of your Beacon you must sacrifice an Emerald, Diamond, Gold or Iron Ingot in the payment slot. Once set, the powers will emanate from the Beacon indefinitely.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BEACON_OVERVIEW">
		<value>At the top of this pyramid there is an inactivate Beacon.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_BEACON_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about Beacons.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about Beacons.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BEACON_PURPOSE">
		<value>Active Beacons project a bright beam of light into the sky and grant powers to nearby players. They are crafted with Glass, Obsidian and Nether Stars, which can be obtained by defeating the Wither.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BEACON_DESIGN">
		<value>Beacons must be placed so that they are in sunlight during the day. Beacons must be placed on Pyramids of Iron, Gold, Emerald or Diamond. However the choice of material has no effect on the power of the beacon.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BEACON_CHOOSING_POWERS">
		<value>Try using the Beacon to set the powers it grants, you can use the Iron Ingots provided as the necessary payment.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HOPPER_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This room contains Hoppers</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_HOPPER_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about Hoppers.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about Hoppers.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HOPPER_PURPOSE">
		<value>Hoppers are used to insert or remove items from containers, and to automatically pick-up items thrown into them.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HOPPER_CONTAINERS">
		<value>They can affect Brewing Stands, Chests, Dispensers, Droppers, Minecarts with Chests, Minecarts with Hoppers, as well as other Hoppers.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HOPPER_MECHANICS">
		<value>Hoppers will continuously attempt to suck items out of suitable container placed above them. It will also attempt to insert stored items into an output container.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HOPPER_REDSTONE">
		<value>However if a Hopper is powered by Redstone it will become inactive and stop both sucking and inserting items.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HOPPER_OUTPUT">
		<value>A Hopper points in the direction it tries to output items. To make a Hopper point to a particular block, place the Hopper against that block whilst sneaking.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_HOPPER_AREA">
		<value>There are various useful Hopper layouts for you to see and experiment with in this room.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>This is the Firework interface, which you can use to craft Fireworks and Firework Stars.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_FIREWORK_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to continue.{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know how to use the Firework interface.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_BASIC_START">
		<value>To craft a Firework, place Gunpowder and Paper in the 3x3 crafting grid that is shown above your inventory.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_BASIC_STARS">
		<value>You can optionally place multiple Firework Stars in the crafting grid to add them to the Firework.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_BASIC_HEIGHT">
		<value>Filling more slots in the crafting grid with Gunpowder will increase the height at which all the Firework Stars will explode.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_BASIC_CRAFT">
		<value>You can then take the crafted Firework out of the output slot when you wish to craft it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_ADV_START">
		<value>Firework Stars can be crafted by placing Gunpowder and Dye into the crafting grid.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_ADV_COLOUR">
		<value>The Dye will set the color of the explosion of the Firework Star.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_ADV_SHAPE">
		<value>The shape of the Firework Star is set by adding either a Fire Charge, Gold Nugget, Feather or Mob Head.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_ADV_EFFECT">
		<value>A trail or a twinkle can be added using Diamonds or Glowstone Dust.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_MENU_ADV_FADE">
		<value>After a Firework Star has been crafted, you can set the fade color of the Firework Star by crafting it with Dye.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_OVERVIEW">
		<value>Contained within the chests here there are various items used in the creation of FIREWORKS!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_FIREWORK_OVERVIEW">
		<value>{*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about Fireworks. {*B*}
Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about Fireworks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_PURPOSE">
		<value>Fireworks are decorative items that can be launched by hand or from Dispensers. They are crafted using Paper, Gunpowder and optionally a number of Firework Stars.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_CUSTOMISE">
		<value>The colors, fade, shape, size, and effects (such as trails and twinkles) of Firework Stars can be customized by including additional ingredients when crafting.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FIREWORK_CRAFTING">
		<value>Try crafting a Firework at the Crafting Table using an assortment of ingredients from the chests.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SELECT">
		<value>Select</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_USE">
		<value>Use</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_BACK">
		<value>Back</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_EXIT">
		<value>Exit</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CANCEL">
		<value>Cancel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CANCEL_JOIN">
		<value>Cancel Join</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_REFRESH">
		<value>Refresh Online Games List</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PARTY_GAMES">
		<value>Party Games</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_ALL_GAMES">
		<value>All Games</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CHANGE_GROUP">
		<value>Change Group</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SHOW_INVENTORY">
		<value>Show Inventory</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SHOW_DESCRIPTION">
		<value>Show Description</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SHOW_INGREDIENTS">
		<value>Show Ingredients</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CRAFTING">
		<value>Crafting</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CREATE">
		<value>Create</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PICKUPPLACE">
		<value>Take/Place</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PICKUP_GENERIC">
		<value>Take</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PICKUP_ALL">
		<value>Take All</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PICKUP_HALF">
		<value>Take Half</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PLACE_GENERIC">
		<value>Place</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PLACE_ALL">
		<value>Place All</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PLACE_ONE">
		<value>Place One</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DROP_GENERIC">
		<value>Drop</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DROP_ALL">
		<value>Drop All</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DROP_ONE">
		<value>Drop One</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SWAP">
		<value>Swap</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_QUICK_MOVE">
		<value>Quick Move</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CLEAR_QUICK_SELECT">
		<value>Clear Quick Select</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_WHAT_IS_THIS">
		<value>What's This?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SHARE">
		<value>Share To Facebook</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CHANGE_FILTER">
		<value>Change Filter</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SEND_FRIEND_REQUEST">
		<value>Send Friend Request</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PAGE_DOWN">
		<value>Page Down</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PAGE_UP">
		<value>Page Up</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_NEXT">
		<value>Next</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PREVIOUS">
		<value>Previous</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_KICK">
		<value>Kick Player</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DYE">
		<value>Dye</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_MINE">
		<value>Mine</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_FEED">
		<value>Feed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_TAME">
		<value>Tame</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_HEAL">
		<value>Heal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SIT">
		<value>Sit</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_FOLLOWME">
		<value>Follow Me</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_EJECT">
		<value>Eject</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_EMPTY">
		<value>Empty</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SADDLE">
		<value>Saddle</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PLACE">
		<value>Place</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_HIT">
		<value>Hit</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_MILK">
		<value>Milk</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_COLLECT">
		<value>Collect</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_EAT">
		<value>Eat</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SLEEP">
		<value>Sleep</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_WAKEUP">
		<value>Wake Up</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PLAY">
		<value>Play</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_RIDE">
		<value>Ride</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SAIL">
		<value>Sail</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_GROW">
		<value>Grow</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SWIMUP">
		<value>Swim Up</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_OPEN">
		<value>Open</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CHANGEPITCH">
		<value>Change Pitch</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DETONATE">
		<value>Detonate</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_READ">
		<value>Read</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_HANG">
		<value>Hang</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_THROW">
		<value>Throw</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PLANT">
		<value>Plant</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_TILL">
		<value>Till</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_HARVEST">
		<value>Harvest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CONTINUE">
		<value>Continue</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_UNLOCKFULLVERSION">
		<value>Unlock Full Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DELETESAVE">
		<value>Delete Save</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DELETE">
		<value>Delete</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_OPTIONS">
		<value>Options</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_INVITE_FRIENDS">
		<value>Invite Friends</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_ACCEPT">
		<value>Accept</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SHEAR">
		<value>Shear</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_BANLEVEL">
		<value>Ban Level</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SELECT_SKIN">
		<value>Select Skin</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_IGNITE">
		<value>Ignite</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_NAVIGATE">
		<value>Navigate</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_INSTALL_FULL">
		<value>Install Full Version</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_INSTALL_TRIAL">
		<value>Install Trial Version</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_INSTALL">
		<value>Install</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_REINSTALL">
		<value>Reinstall</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SAVEOPTIONS">
		<value>Save Options</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_EXECUTE_COMMAND">
		<value>Execute Command</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CREATIVE">
		<value>Creative</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_QUICK_MOVE_INGREDIENT">
		<value>Move Ingredient</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_QUICK_MOVE_FUEL">
		<value>Move Fuel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_QUICK_MOVE_TOOL">
		<value>Move Tool</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_QUICK_MOVE_ARMOR">
		<value>Move Armor</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_QUICK_MOVE_WEAPON">
		<value>Move Weapon</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_EQUIP">
		<value>Equip</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DRAW_BOW">
		<value>Draw</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_RELEASE_BOW">
		<value>Release</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PRIVILEGES">
		<value>Privileges</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_BLOCK">
		<value>Block</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PAGEUP">
		<value>Page Up</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_PAGEDOWN">
		<value>Page Down</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_LOVEMODE">
		<value>Love Mode</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DRINK">
		<value>Drink</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_ROTATE">
		<value>Rotate</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_HIDE">
		<value>Hide</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CLEARSLOTS">
		<value>Clear All Slots</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_MOUNT">
		<value>Mount</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DISMOUNT">
		<value>Dismount</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SADDLEBAGS">
		<value>Attach Chest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_FIREWORK_LAUNCH">
		<value>Launch</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_LEASH">
		<value>Leash</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_UNLEASH">
		<value>Release</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_ATTACH">
		<value>Attach</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_NAME">
		<value>Name</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_OK">
		<value>OK</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_CANCEL">
		<value>Cancel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DOWNLOADABLECONTENT">
		<value>Minecraft Store</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_LEAVE_VIA_INVITE">
		<value>Are you sure you want to leave your current game and join the new one? Any unsaved progress will be lost.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_EXIT_GAME">
		<value>Exit Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TITLE_SAVE_GAME">
		<value>Save Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TITLE_DECLINE_SAVE_GAME">
		<value>Exit Without Saving</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_SAVE_GAME">
		<value>Are you sure you want to overwrite any previous save for this world with the current version of this world?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_DECLINE_SAVE_GAME">
		<value>Are you sure you want to exit without saving? You will lose all progress in this world!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TITLE_START_GAME">
		<value>Start Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CORRUPT_OR_DAMAGED_SAVE_TITLE">
		<value>Damaged Save</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CORRUPT_OR_DAMAGED_SAVE_TEXT">
		<value>This save is corrupt or damaged. Would you like to delete it?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_EXIT_GAME_CONFIRM_DISCONNECT_SAVE">
		<value>Are you sure you want to exit to the main menu and disconnect all players from the game? Any unsaved progress will be lost.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_EXIT_GAME_SAVE">
		<value>Exit and save</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_EXIT_GAME_NO_SAVE">
		<value>Exit without saving</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_EXIT_GAME">
		<value>Are you sure you want to exit to the main menu? Any unsaved progress will be lost.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_EXIT_GAME_PROGRESS_LOST">
		<value>Are you sure you want to exit to the main menu? Your progress will be lost!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREATE_NEW_WORLD">
		<value>Create New World</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAY_TUTORIAL">
		<value>Play Tutorial</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIALSAVENAME">
		<value>Tutorial</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NAME_WORLD">
		<value>Name Your World</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NAME_WORLD_TEXT">
		<value>Enter a name for your world</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREATE_NEW_WORLD_SEEDTEXT">
		<value>Input the seed for your world generation</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LOAD_SAVED_WORLD">
		<value>Load Saved World</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRESS_START_TO_JOIN">
		<value>Press START to join game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_EXITING_GAME">
		<value>Exiting the game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GENERIC_ERROR">
		<value>An error occurred. Exiting to the main menu.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONNECTION_FAILED">
		<value>Connection failed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONNECTION_LOST">
		<value>Connection lost</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONNECTION_LOST_SERVER">
		<value>Connection to the server was lost. Exiting to the main menu.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED">
		<value>Disconnected by the server</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_KICKED">
		<value>You were kicked from the game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_FLYING">
		<value>You were kicked from the game for flying</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_LOGIN_TOO_LONG">
		<value>Connection attempt took too long</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_SERVER_FULL">
		<value>The server is full</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_SERVER_QUIT">
		<value>The host has exited the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_NO_FRIENDS_IN_GAME">
		<value>You cannot join this game as you are not friends with anybody in the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_BANNED">
		<value>You cannot join this game as you have previously been kicked by the host.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_SERVER_OLD">
		<value>You cannot join this game as the player you are trying to join is running an older version of the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_CLIENT_OLD">
		<value>You cannot join this game as the player you are trying to join is running a newer version of the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEFAULT_SAVENAME">
		<value>New World</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_AWARD_TITLE">
		<value>Award Unlocked!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_AWARD_GAMERPIC1">
		<value>Hurray - you've been awarded a gamerpic featuring Steve from Minecraft!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_AWARD_GAMERPIC2">
		<value>Hurray - you've been awarded a gamerpic featuring a Creeper!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_TITLE">
		<value>Unlock Full Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_TOSAVE_TEXT">
		<value>You're playing the trial game, but you'll need the full game to be able to save your game.
Would you like to unlock the full game now?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARD_LOADING">
		<value>Please wait</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARD_NORESULTS">
		<value>No results</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARD_FILTER">
		<value>Filter: </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARD_FILTER_FRIENDS">
		<value>Friends</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARD_FILTER_MYSCORE">
		<value>My Score</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARD_FILTER_OVERALL">
		<value>Overall</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARD_ENTRIES">
		<value>Entries: </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARD_RANK">
		<value>Rank</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_SAVING_LEVEL">
		<value>Preparing to Save Level</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_SAVING_CHUNKS">
		<value>Preparing Chunks...</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_SAVING_TO_DISC">
		<value>Finalizing...</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_BUILDING_TERRAIN">
		<value>Building Terrain</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_SIMULATING_WORLD">
		<value>Simulating world for a bit</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_INITIALISING_SERVER">
		<value>Initializing server</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_GENERATING_SPAWN_AREA">
		<value>Generating spawn area</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_LOADING_SPAWN_AREA">
		<value>Loading spawn area</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_ENTERING_NETHER">
		<value>Entering The Nether</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_LEAVING_NETHER">
		<value>Leaving The Nether</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_RESPAWNING">
		<value>Respawning</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_GENERATING_LEVEL">
		<value>Generating level</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_LOADING_LEVEL">
		<value>Loading level</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_SAVING_PLAYERS">
		<value>Saving players</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_CONNECTING">
		<value>Connecting to host</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_DOWNLOADING_TERRAIN">
		<value>Downloading terrain</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_CONVERTING_TO_OFFLINE_GAME">
		<value>Switching to offline game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_HOST_SAVING">
		<value>Please wait while the host saves the game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_ENTERING_END">
		<value>Entering The END</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_LEAVING_END">
		<value>Leaving The END</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_NEW_WORLD_SEED">
		<value>Finding Seed for the World Generator</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BED_OCCUPIED">
		<value>This bed is occupied</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BED_NO_SLEEP">
		<value>You can only sleep at night</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BED_PLAYERSLEEP">
		<value>%s is sleeping in a bed. To skip to dawn, all players need to sleep in beds at the same time.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BED_NOT_VALID">
		<value>Your home bed was missing or obstructed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BED_NOTSAFE">
		<value>You may not rest now, there are monsters nearby</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_BED_MESLEEP">
		<value>You are sleeping in a bed. To skip to dawn, all players need to sleep in beds at the same time.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_TOOLS">
		<value>Tools and Weapons</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_WEAPONS">
		<value>Weapons</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_FOOD">
		<value>Food</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_STRUCTURES">
		<value>Structures</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_ARMOUR">
		<value>Armor</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_MECHANISMS">
		<value>Mechanisms</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_TRANSPORT">
		<value>Transport</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_DECORATIONS">
		<value>Decorations</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_BUILDING_BLOCKS">
		<value>Building Blocks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_REDSTONE_AND_TRANSPORT">
		<value>Redstone &amp; Transportation</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_MISCELLANEOUS">
		<value>Miscellaneous</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_POTIONS">
		<value>Brewing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_TOOLS_WEAPONS_ARMOR">
		<value>Tools, Weapons &amp; Armor</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_MATERIALS">
		<value>Materials</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RETURNEDTOMENU_TITLE">
		<value>Signed out</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_DIFFICULTY">
		<value>Difficulty</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_MUSIC">
		<value>Music</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_SOUND">
		<value>Sound</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_GAMMA">
		<value>Gamma</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_SENSITIVITY_INGAME">
		<value>Game Sensitivity</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_SENSITIVITY_INMENU">
		<value>Interface Sensitivity</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DIFFICULTY_TITLE_PEACEFUL">
		<value>Peaceful</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DIFFICULTY_TITLE_EASY">
		<value>Easy</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DIFFICULTY_TITLE_NORMAL">
		<value>Normal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DIFFICULTY_TITLE_HARD">
		<value>Hard</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DIFFICULTY_PEACEFUL">
		<value>In this mode, the player regains health over time, and there are no enemies in the environment.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DIFFICULTY_EASY">
		<value>In this mode, enemies spawn in the environment, but will do less damage to the player than in the Normal mode.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DIFFICULTY_NORMAL">
		<value>In this mode, enemies spawn in the environment and will do a standard amount of damage to the player.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DIFFICULTY_HARD">
		<value>In this mode, enemies will spawn in the environment, and will do a great deal of damage to the player. Watch out for the Creepers too, since they are unlikely to cancel their exploding attack when you move away from them!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TRIALOVER_TITLE">
		<value>Trial Timeout</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MULTIPLAYER_FULL_TITLE">
		<value>Game full</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MULTIPLAYER_FULL_TEXT">
		<value>Failed to join game as there are no spaces left</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SIGN_TITLE">
		<value>Enter Sign Text</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SIGN_TITLE_TEXT">
		<value>Enter a line of text for your sign</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NAME_TITLE">
		<value>Enter Title</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NAME_TITLE_TEXT">
		<value>Enter a title for your post</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NAME_CAPTION">
		<value>Enter Caption</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NAME_CAPTION_TEXT">
		<value>Enter a caption for your post</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NAME_DESC">
		<value>Enter Description</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NAME_DESC_TEXT">
		<value>Enter a description for your post</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_INVENTORY">
		<value>Inventory</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_INGREDIENTS">
		<value>Ingredients</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_BREWING_STAND">
		<value>Brewing Stand</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHEST">
		<value>Chest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANT">
		<value>Enchant</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FURNACE">
		<value>Furnace</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_INGREDIENT">
		<value>Ingredient</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FUEL">
		<value>Fuel</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISPENSER">
		<value>Dispenser</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTAINER_ANIMAL">
		<value>Horse</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTAINER_DROPPER">
		<value>Dropper</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTAINER_HOPPER">
		<value>Hopper</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTAINER_BEACON">
		<value>Beacon</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTAINER_BEACON_PRIMARY_POWER">
		<value>Primary Power</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTAINER_BEACON_SECONDARY_POWER">
		<value>Secondary Power</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTAINER_MINECART">
		<value>Minecart</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NO_DLCOFFERS">
		<value>There are no downloadable content offers of this type available for this title at the moment.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAYER_JOINED">
		<value>%s has joined the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAYER_LEFT">
		<value>%s has left the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAYER_KICKED">
		<value>%s was kicked from the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TEXT_DELETE_SAVE">
		<value>Are you sure you want to delete this save game?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_STRINGVERIFY_AWAITING_APPROVAL">
		<value>Awaiting approval</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_STRINGVERIFY_CENSORED">
		<value>Censored</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NOWPLAYING">
		<value>Now playing: </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEFAULTS_TITLE">
		<value>Reset Settings</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEFAULTS_TEXT">
		<value>Are you sure you would like to reset your settings to their default values?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FATAL_ERROR_TITLE">
		<value>Loading Error</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAME_HOST_NAME">
		<value>%s's Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAME_HOST_NAME_UNKNOWN">
		<value>Unknown host game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GUEST_ORDER_CHANGED_TITLE">
		<value>Guest signed out</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GUEST_ORDER_CHANGED_TEXT">
		<value>A guest player has signed out causing all guest players to be removed from the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MUST_SIGN_IN_TITLE">
		<value>Sign in</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MUST_SIGN_IN_TEXT">
		<value>You are not signed in.  In order to play this game, you will need to be signed in.  Do you want to sign in now?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NO_MULTIPLAYER_PRIVILEGE_TITLE">
		<value>Multiplayer not allowed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FAILED_TO_CREATE_GAME_TITLE">
		<value>Failed to create game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEFAULT_SKINS">
		<value>Auto Selected</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NO_SKIN_PACK">
		<value>No Pack: Default Skins</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FAVORITES_SKIN_PACK">
		<value>Favorite Skins</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_BANNED_LEVEL_TITLE">
		<value>Banned Level</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAYER_BANNED_LEVEL">
		<value>The game you are joining is in your banned level list. 
If you choose to join this game, the level will be removed from your banned level list.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ACTION_BAN_LEVEL_TITLE">
		<value>Ban This Level?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ACTION_BAN_LEVEL_DESCRIPTION">
		<value>Are you sure you want to add this level to your banned level list? 
Selecting OK will also exit this game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_BUTTON_REMOVE_FROM_BAN_LIST">
		<value>Remove from Banned List</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_AUTOSAVE">
		<value>Autosave Interval</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_AUTOSAVE_OFF">
		<value>Autosave Interval: OFF</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MINUTES">
		<value>Mins</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CANT_PLACE_NEAR_SPAWN_TITLE">
		<value>Can't Place Here!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CANT_PLACE_NEAR_SPAWN_TEXT">
		<value>Placing lava close to the level spawn point is not allowed due to the possibility of instant death for spawning players.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_INTERFACEOPACITY">
		<value>Interface Opacity</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PROGRESS_AUTOSAVING_LEVEL">
		<value>Preparing to Autosave Level</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_UISIZE">
		<value>HUD Size</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SLIDER_UISIZESPLITSCREEN">
		<value>HUD Size (Splitscreen)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SEED">
		<value>Seed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_DLC_TITLE">
		<value>Unlock Skin Pack</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_DLC_SKIN">
		<value>To use the skin you have selected, you need to unlock this skin pack.
Would you like to unlock this skin pack now?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_DLC_TEXTUREPACK_TITLE">
		<value>Unlock Texture Pack</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_DLC_TEXTUREPACK_TEXT">
		<value>To use this texture pack for your world, you need to unlock it.
Would you like to unlock it now?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WARNING_DLC_TRIALTEXTUREPACK_TITLE">
		<value>Trial Texture Pack</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WARNING_DLC_TRIALTEXTUREPACK_TEXT">
		<value>You are using a trial version of the texture pack. You will not be able to save this world unless you unlock the full version. 
Would you like to unlock the full version of the texture pack?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_TEXTUREPACK_NOT_PRESENT_TITLE">
		<value>Texture Pack Not Present</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_TEXTUREPACK_UNLOCK_TITLE">
		<value>Unlock Full Version</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_TEXTUREPACK_GET_TRIAL_TITLE">
		<value>Download Trial Version</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_TEXTUREPACK_GET_FULL_TITLE">
		<value>Download Full Version</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_TEXTUREPACK_NOT_PRESENT">
		<value>This world uses a mash-up pack or texture pack you don't have!
Would you like to install the mash-up pack or texture pack now?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TEXTURE_PACK_TRIALVERSION">
		<value>Get Trial Version</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TEXTUREPACK_FULLVERSION">
		<value>Get Full Version</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_KICK_PLAYER_TITLE">
		<value>Kick player</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_KICK_PLAYER">
		<value>Are you sure you want to kick this player from the game? They will not be able to rejoin until you restart the world.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMERPICS">
		<value>Gamerpics Packs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_THEMES">
		<value>Themes</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SKINS">
		<value>Skins Packs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ALLOWFRIENDSOFFRIENDS">
		<value>Allow friends of friends</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NOTALLOWED_FRIENDSOFFRIENDS">
		<value>You cannot join this game because it has been limited to players who are friends of the host.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CANTJOIN_TITLE">
		<value>Can't Join Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SELECTED">
		<value>Selected</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SELECTED_SKIN">
		<value>Selected skin:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CORRUPT_DLC_TITLE">
		<value>Corrupt Downloadable Content</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CORRUPT_DLC">
		<value>This downloadable content is corrupt and cannot be used. You need to delete it, then re-install it from the Minecraft Store menu.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CORRUPT_DLC_MULTIPLE">
		<value>Some of your downloadable content is corrupt and cannot be used. You need to delete them, then re-install them from the Minecraft Store menu.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAME_MODE_CHANGED">
		<value>Your game mode has been changed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RENAME_WORLD_TITLE">
		<value>Rename Your World</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RENAME_WORLD_TEXT">
		<value>Enter the new name for your world</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEMODE_SURVIVAL">
		<value>Game Mode: Survival</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEMODE_CREATIVE">
		<value>Game Mode: Creative</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEMODE_ADVENTURE">
		<value>Game Mode: Adventure</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SURVIVAL">
		<value>Survival</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREATIVE">
		<value>Creative</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ADVENTURE">
		<value>Adventure</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREATED_IN_SURVIVAL">
		<value>Created in Survival Mode</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREATED_IN_CREATIVE">
		<value>Created in Creative Mode</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHECKBOX_RENDER_CLOUDS">
		<value>Render Clouds</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TEXT_SAVEOPTIONS">
		<value>What would you like to do with this save game?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TITLE_RENAMESAVE">
		<value>Rename Save</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_AUTOSAVE_COUNTDOWN">
		<value>Autosaving in %d...</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ON">
		<value>On</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_OFF">
		<value>Off</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEVELTYPE_NORMAL">
		<value>Normal</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEVELTYPE_SUPERFLAT">
		<value>Superflat</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_SEED">
		<value>Enter a seed to generate the same terrain again. Leave blank for a random world.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_ONLINE">
		<value>When enabled, the game will be an online game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_INVITEONLY">
		<value>When enabled, only invited players can join.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_ALLOWFOF">
		<value>When enabled, friends of people on your Friends List can join the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_PVP">
		<value>When enabled, players can inflict damage on other players. Only affects Survival mode.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_TRUST">
		<value>When disabled, players joining the game cannot build or mine until authorised.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_FIRE_SPREADS">
		<value>When enabled, fire may spread to nearby flammable blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_TNT_EXPLODES">
		<value>When enabled, TNT will explode when activated.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_RESET_NETHER">
		<value>When enabled, the Nether world will be re-generated. This is useful if you have an older save where Nether Fortresses were not present.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_STRUCTURES">
		<value>When enabled, structures such as Villages and Strongholds will generate in the world.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_SUPERFLAT">
		<value>When enabled, a completely flat world will be generated in the Overworld and in the Nether.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_BONUS_CHEST">
		<value>When enabled, a chest containing some useful items will be created near the player spawn point.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_MOB_GRIEFING">
		<value>When disabled, prevents monsters and animals from changing blocks (for example, Creeper explosions won't destroy blocks and Sheep won't remove Grass) or picking up items.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_KEEP_INVENTORY">
		<value>When enabled, players will keep their inventory when they die.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_MOB_SPAWNING">
		<value>When disabled, mobs will not spawn naturally.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_MOB_LOOT">
		<value>When disabled, monsters and animals will not drop loot (for example, Creepers won't drop gunpowder).</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_TILE_DROPS">
		<value>When disabled, blocks will not drop items when destroyed (for example, Stone blocks won't drop Cobblestone).</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_NATURAL_REGEN">
		<value>When disabled, players will not regenerate health naturally.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_DAYLIGHT_CYCLE">
		<value>When disabled, the time of day will not change.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_MENU_SKINPACKS">
		<value>Skin Packs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_MENU_THEMES">
		<value>Themes</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_MENU_GAMERPICS">
		<value>Gamerpics</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_MENU_AVATARITEMS">
		<value>Avatar Items</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_MENU_TEXTUREPACKS">
		<value>Texture Packs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_MENU_MASHUPPACKS">
		<value>Mash-Up Packs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_INFIRE">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} went up in flames</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_ONFIRE">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} burned to death</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_LAVA">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} tried to swim in lava</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_INWALL">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} suffocated in a wall</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_DROWN">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} drowned</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_STARVE">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} starved to death</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_CACTUS">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was pricked to death</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FALL">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} hit the ground too hard</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_OUTOFWORLD">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} fell out of the world</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_GENERIC">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} died</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_EXPLOSION">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} blew up</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_MAGIC">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was killed by magic</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_DRAGON_BREATH">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was killed by Ender Dragon breath</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_MOB">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was slain by {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_PLAYER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was slain by {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_ARROW">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was shot by {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FIREBALL">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was fireballed by {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_THROWN">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was pummeled by {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_INDIRECT_MAGIC">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was killed by {*SOURCE*} using magic</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FELL_ACCIDENT_LADDER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} fell off a ladder</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FELL_ACCIDENT_VINES">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} fell off some vines</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FELL_ACCIDENT_WATER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} fell out of the water</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FELL_ACCIDENT_GENERIC">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} fell from a high place</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FELL_KILLER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was doomed to fall by {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FELL_ASSIST">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was doomed to fall by {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FELL_ASSIST_ITEM">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was doomed to fall by {*SOURCE*} using {*ITEM*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FELL_FINISH">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} fell too far and was finished by {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FELL_FINISH_ITEM">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} fell too far and was finished by {*SOURCE*} using {*ITEM*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_INFIRE_PLAYER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} walked into fire whilst fighting {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_ONFIRE_PLAYER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was burnt to a crisp whilst fighting {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_LAVA_PLAYER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} tried to swim in lava to escape {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_DROWN_PLAYER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} drowned whilst trying to escape {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_CACTUS_PLAYER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} walked into a cactus whilst trying to escape {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_EXPLOSION_PLAYER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was blown up by {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_WITHER">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} withered away</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_PLAYER_ITEM">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was slain by {*SOURCE*} using {*ITEM*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_ARROW_ITEM">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was shot by {*SOURCE*} using {*ITEM*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FIREBALL_ITEM">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was fireballed by {*SOURCE*} using {*ITEM*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_THROWN_ITEM">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was pummeled by {*SOURCE*} using {*ITEM*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_INDIRECT_MAGIC_ITEM">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was killed by {*SOURCE*} using {*ITEM*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHECKBOX_RENDER_BEDROCKFOG">
		<value>Bedrock Fog</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHECKBOX_DISPLAY_HUD">
		<value>Display HUD</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHECKBOX_DISPLAY_HAND">
		<value>Display Hand</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHECKBOX_DEATH_MESSAGES">
		<value>Death Messages</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHECKBOX_ANIMATED_CHARACTER">
		<value>Animated Character</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHECKBOX_CUSTOM_SKIN_ANIM">
		<value>Custom Skin Animation</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_MINE_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can no longer mine or use items</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_MINE_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can now mine and use items</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_BUILD_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can no longer place blocks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_BUILD_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can now place blocks</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_USE_DOORS_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can now use doors and switches</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_USE_DOORS_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can no longer use doors and switches</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_USE_CONTAINERS_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can now use containers (e.g. chests)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_USE_CONTAINERS_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can no longer use containers (e.g. chests)</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_ATTACK_MOB_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can no longer attack mobs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_ATTACK_MOB_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can now attack mobs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_ATTACK_PLAYER_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can no longer attack players</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_ATTACK_PLAYER_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can now attack players</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_ATTACK_ANIMAL_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can no longer attack animals</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_ATTACK_ANIMAL_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can now attack animals</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_MODERATOR_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You are now a moderator</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_MODERATOR_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You are no longer a moderator</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_FLY_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can now fly</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_FLY_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can no longer fly</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_EXHAUSTION_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You will no longer get exhausted</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_EXHAUSTION_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You will now get exhausted</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_INVISIBLE_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You are now invisible</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_INVISIBLE_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You are no longer invisible</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_INVULNERABLE_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You are now invulnerable</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_INVULNERABLE_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You are no longer invulnerable</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DLC_COST">
		<value>%d MSP</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_BOSS_ENDERDRAGON_HEALTH">
		<value>Ender Dragon</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAYER_ENTERED_END">
		<value>%s has entered The End</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAYER_LEFT_END">
		<value>%s has left The End</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WIN_TEXT">
		<value>
{*C3*}I see the player you mean.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}{*PLAYER*}?{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Yes. Take care. It has reached a higher level now. It can read our thoughts.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}That doesn't matter. It thinks we are part of the game.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}I like this player. It played well. It did not give up.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}It is reading our thoughts as though they were words on a screen.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}That is how it chooses to imagine many things, when it is deep in the dream of a game.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Words make a wonderful interface. Very flexible. And less terrifying than staring at the reality behind the screen.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}They used to hear voices. Before players could read. Back in the days when those who did not play called the players witches, and warlocks. And players dreamed they flew through the air, on sticks powered by demons.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}What did this player dream?{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}This player dreamed of sunlight and trees. Of fire and water. It dreamed it created. And it dreamed it destroyed. It dreamed it hunted, and was hunted. It dreamed of shelter.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Hah, the original interface. A million years old, and it still works. But what true structure did this player create, in the reality behind the screen?{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}It worked, with a million others, to sculpt a true world in a fold of the {*EF*}{*NOISE*}{*C3*}, and created a {*EF*}{*NOISE*}{*C3*} for {*EF*}{*NOISE*}{*C3*}, in the {*EF*}{*NOISE*}{*C3*}.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}It cannot read that thought.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}No. It has not yet achieved the highest level. That, it must achieve in the long dream of life, not the short dream of a game.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Does it know that we love it? That the universe is kind?{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Sometimes, through the noise of its thoughts, it hears the universe, yes.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}But there are times it is sad, in the long dream. It creates worlds that have no summer, and it shivers under a black sun, and it takes its sad creation for reality.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}To cure it of sorrow would destroy it. The sorrow is part of its own private task. We cannot interfere.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Sometimes when they are deep in dreams, I want to tell them, they are building true worlds in reality. Sometimes I want to tell them of their importance to the universe. Sometimes, when they have not made a true connection in a while, I want to help them to speak the word they fear.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}It reads our thoughts.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Sometimes I do not care. Sometimes I wish to tell them, this world you take for truth is merely {*EF*}{*NOISE*}{*C2*} and {*EF*}{*NOISE*}{*C2*}, I wish to tell them that they are {*EF*}{*NOISE*}{*C2*} in the {*EF*}{*NOISE*}{*C2*}. They see so little of reality, in their long dream.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}And yet they play the game.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}But it would be so easy to tell them...{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Too strong for this dream. To tell them how to live is to prevent them living.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}I will not tell the player how to live.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}The player is growing restless.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}I will tell the player a story.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}But not the truth.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}No. A story that contains the truth safely, in a cage of words. Not the naked truth that can burn over any distance.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Give it a body, again.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Yes. Player...{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Use its name.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}{*PLAYER*}. Player of games.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Good.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WIN_TEXT_PART_2">
		<value>
{*C2*}Take a breath, now. Take another. Feel air in your lungs. Let your limbs return. Yes, move your fingers. Have a body again, under gravity, in air. Respawn in the long dream. There you are. Your body touching the universe again at every point, as though you were separate things. As though we were separate things.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Who are we? Once we were called the spirit of the mountain. Father sun, mother moon. Ancestral spirits, animal spirits. Jinn. Ghosts. The green man. Then gods, demons. Angels. Poltergeists. Aliens, extraterrestrials. Leptons, quarks. The words change. We do not change.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}We are the universe. We are everything you think isn't you. You are looking at us now, through your skin and your eyes. And why does the universe touch your skin, and throw light on you? To see you, player. To know you. And to be known. I shall tell you a story.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Once upon a time, there was a player.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}The player was you, {*PLAYER*}.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Sometimes it thought itself human, on the thin crust of a spinning globe of molten rock. The ball of molten rock circled a ball of blazing gas that was three hundred and thirty thousand times more massive than it. They were so far apart that light took eight minutes to cross the gap. The light was information from a star, and it could burn your skin from a hundred and fifty million kilometres away.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Sometimes the player dreamed it was a miner, on the surface of a world that was flat, and infinite. The sun was a square of white. The days were short; there was much to do; and death was a temporary inconvenience.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Sometimes the player dreamed it was lost in a story.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Sometimes the player dreamed it was other things, in other places. Sometimes these dreams were disturbing. Sometimes very beautiful indeed. Sometimes the player woke from one dream into another, then woke from that into a third.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Sometimes the player dreamed it watched words on a screen.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Let's go back.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}The atoms of the player were scattered in the grass, in the rivers, in the air, in the ground. A woman gathered the atoms; she drank and ate and inhaled; and the woman assembled the player, in her body.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}And the player awoke, from the warm, dark world of its mother's body, into the long dream.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}And the player was a new story, never told before, written in letters of DNA. And the player was a new program, never run before, generated by a sourcecode a billion years old. And the player was a new human, never alive before, made from nothing but milk and love.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}You are the player. The story. The program. The human. Made from nothing but milk and love.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Let's go further back.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}The seven billion billion billion atoms of the player's body were created, long before this game, in the heart of a star. So the player, too, is information from a star. And the player moves through a story, which is a forest of information planted by a man called Julian, on a flat, infinite world created by a man called Markus, that exists inside a small, private world created by the player, who inhabits a universe created by...{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}Shush. Sometimes the player created a small, private world that was soft and warm and simple. Sometimes hard, and cold, and complicated. Sometimes it built a model of the universe in its head; flecks of energy, moving through vast empty spaces. Sometimes it called those flecks "electrons" and "protons".{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WIN_TEXT_PART_3">
		<value>
{*C2*}Sometimes it called them "planets" and "stars".{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Sometimes it believed it was in a universe that was made of energy that was made of offs and ons; zeros and ones; lines of code. Sometimes it believed it was playing a game. Sometimes it believed it was reading words on a screen.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}You are the player, reading words...{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Shush... Sometimes the player read lines of code on a screen. Decoded them into words; decoded words into meaning; decoded meaning into feelings, emotions, theories, ideas, and the player started to breathe faster and deeper and realised it was alive, it was alive, those thousand deaths had not been real, the player was alive{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}You. You. You are alive.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}and sometimes the player believed the universe had spoken to it through the sunlight that came through the shuffling leaves of the summer trees{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}and sometimes the player believed the universe had spoken to it through the light that fell from the crisp night sky of winter, where a fleck of light in the corner of the player's eye might be a star a million times as massive as the sun, boiling its planets to plasma in order to be visible for a moment to the player, walking home at the far side of the universe, suddenly smelling food, almost at the familiar door, about to dream again{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}and sometimes the player believed the universe had spoken to it through the zeros and ones, through the electricity of the world, through the scrolling words on a screen at the end of a dream{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}and the universe said I love you{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}and the universe said you have played the game well{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}and the universe said everything you need is within you{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}and the universe said you are stronger than you know{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}and the universe said you are the daylight{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}and the universe said you are the night{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}and the universe said the darkness you fight is within you{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}and the universe said the light you seek is within you{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}and the universe said you are not alone{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}and the universe said you are not separate from every other thing{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}and the universe said you are the universe tasting itself, talking to itself, reading its own code{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}and the universe said I love you because you are love.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}And the game was over and the player woke up from the dream. And the player began a new dream. And the player dreamed again, dreamed better. And the player was the universe. And the player was love.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C3*}You are the player.{*EF*}{*B*}{*B*}
{*C2*}Wake up.{*EF*}
</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RESETNETHER_TITLE">
		<value>Reset Nether</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RESETNETHER_TEXT">
		<value>Are you sure you want to reset the Nether in this savegame to its default state? You will lose anything you have built in the Nether!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RESET_NETHER">
		<value>Reset Nether</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DONT_RESET_NETHER">
		<value>Don't Reset Nether</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CANT_SHEAR_MOOSHROOM">
		<value>Can't shear this Mooshroom at the moment. The maximum number of Pigs, Sheep, Cows, Cats and Horses has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_PIGS_SHEEP_COWS_CATS_SPAWNED">
		<value>Can't use Spawn Egg at the moment. The maximum number of Pigs, Sheep, Cows, Cats and Horses has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_MOOSHROOMS_SPAWNED">
		<value>Can't use Spawn Egg at the moment. The maximum number of Mooshrooms has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_WOLVES_SPAWNED">
		<value>Can't use Spawn Egg at the moment. The maximum number of Wolves in a world has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_CHICKENS_SPAWNED">
		<value>Can't use Spawn Egg at the moment. The maximum number of Chickens in a world has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_SQUID_SPAWNED">
		<value>Can't use Spawn Egg at the moment. The maximum number of Squid in a world has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_BATS_SPAWNED">
		<value>Can't use Spawn Egg at the moment. The maximum number of Bats in a world has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_ENEMIES_SPAWNED">
		<value>Can't use Spawn Egg at the moment. The maximum number of enemies in a world has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_VILLAGERS_SPAWNED">
		<value>Can't use Spawn Egg at the moment. The maximum number of villagers in a world has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_HANGINGENTITIES">
		<value>The maximum number of Paintings/Item Frames in a world has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CANT_SPAWN_IN_PEACEFUL">
		<value>You can't spawn enemies in Peaceful mode.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_PIGS_SHEEP_COWS_CATS_BRED">
		<value>This animal can't enter Love Mode. The maximum number of breeding Pigs, Sheep, Cows, Cats and Horses has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_WOLVES_BRED">
		<value>This animal can't enter Love Mode. The maximum number of breeding Wolves has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_CHICKENS_BRED">
		<value>This animal can't enter Love Mode. The maximum number of breeding Chickens has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_HORSES_BRED">
		<value>This animal can't enter Love Mode. The maximum number of breeding horses has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_MUSHROOMCOWS_BRED">
		<value>This animal can't enter Love Mode. The maximum number of breeding Mooshrooms has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_BOATS">
		<value>The maximum number of Boats in a world has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MAX_SKULL_TILES">
		<value>The maximum number of Mob Heads in a world has been reached.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_INVERT_LOOK">
		<value>Invert Look</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SOUTHPAW">
		<value>Southpaw</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_YOU_DIED">
		<value>You Died!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RESPAWN">
		<value>Respawn</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DOWNLOADABLE_CONTENT_OFFERS">
		<value>Downloadable Content Offers</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHANGE_SKIN">
		<value>Change Skin</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY">
		<value>How To Play</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROLS">
		<value>Controls</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SETTINGS">
		<value>Settings</value>
	</data>	

  <data name="IDS_LANGUAGE_SELECTOR">
    <value>Languages</value>
  </data>

	<data name="IDS_CREDITS">
		<value>Credits</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REINSTALL_CONTENT">
		<value>Reinstall Content</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEBUG_SETTINGS">
		<value>Debug Settings</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FIRE_SPREADS">
		<value>Fire Spreads</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TNT_EXPLODES">
		<value>TNT Explodes</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAYER_VS_PLAYER">
		<value>Player vs Player</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TRUST_PLAYERS">
		<value>Trust Players</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOST_PRIVILEGES">
		<value>Host Privileges</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GENERATE_STRUCTURES">
		<value>Generate Structures</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SUPERFLAT_WORLD">
		<value>Superflat World</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_BONUS_CHEST">
		<value>Bonus Chest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WORLD_OPTIONS">
		<value>World Options</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAME_OPTIONS">
		<value>Game Options</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MOB_GRIEFING">
		<value>Mob Griefing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_KEEP_INVENTORY">
		<value>Keep Inventory</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MOB_SPAWNING">
		<value>Mob Spawning</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MOB_LOOT">
		<value>Mob Loot</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_DROPS">
		<value>Tile Drops</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NATURAL_REGEN">
		<value>Natural Regeneration</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DAYLIGHT_CYCLE">
		<value>Daylight Cycle</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CAN_BUILD_AND_MINE">
		<value>Can Build and Mine</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CAN_USE_DOORS_AND_SWITCHES">
		<value>Can Use Doors and Switches</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CAN_OPEN_CONTAINERS">
		<value>Can Open Containers</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CAN_ATTACK_PLAYERS">
		<value>Can Attack Players</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CAN_ATTACK_ANIMALS">
		<value>Can Attack Animals</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MODERATOR">
		<value>Moderator</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_KICK_PLAYER">
		<value>Kick Player</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CAN_FLY">
		<value>Can Fly</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DISABLE_EXHAUSTION">
		<value>Disable Exhaustion</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_INVISIBLE">
		<value>Invisible</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOST_OPTIONS">
		<value>Host Options</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAYERS_INVITE">
		<value>Players/Invite</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ONLINE_GAME">
		<value>Online Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_INVITE_ONLY">
		<value>Invite Only</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_MORE_OPTIONS">
		<value>More Options</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LOAD">
		<value>Load</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEFAULT_WORLD_NAME">
		<value>New World</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_WORLD_NAME">
		<value>World Name</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREATE_NEW_WORLD_SEED">
		<value>Seed for the World Generator</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CREATE_NEW_WORLD_RANDOM_SEED">
		<value>Leave blank for a random seed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAYERS">
		<value>Players</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_JOIN_GAME">
		<value>Join Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_START_GAME">
		<value>Start Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NO_GAMES_FOUND">
		<value>No Games Found</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PLAY_GAME">
		<value>Play Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARDS">
		<value>Leaderboards</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HELP_AND_OPTIONS">
		<value>Help &amp; Options</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_FULL_GAME">
		<value>Unlock Full Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RESUME_GAME">
		<value>Resume Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SAVE_GAME">
		<value>Save Game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LABEL_DIFFICULTY">
		<value>Difficulty:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LABEL_GAME_TYPE">
		<value>Game Type:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LABEL_STRUCTURES">
		<value>Structures:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LABEL_LEVEL_TYPE">
		<value>Level Type:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LABEL_PvP">
		<value>PvP:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LABEL_TRUST">
		<value>Trust Players:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LABEL_TNT">
		<value>TNT:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LABEL_FIRE_SPREADS">
		<value>Fire Spreads:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REINSTALL_THEME">
		<value>Reinstall Theme</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REINSTALL_GAMERPIC_1">
		<value>Reinstall Gamerpic 1</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REINSTALL_GAMERPIC_2">
		<value>Reinstall Gamerpic 2</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REINSTALL_AVATAR_ITEM_1">
		<value>Reinstall Avatar Item 1</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REINSTALL_AVATAR_ITEM_2">
		<value>Reinstall Avatar Item 2</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REINSTALL_AVATAR_ITEM_3">
		<value>Reinstall Avatar Item 3</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_OPTIONS">
		<value>Options</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_AUDIO">
		<value>Audio</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONTROL">
		<value>Control</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GRAPHICS">
		<value>Graphics</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_USER_INTERFACE">
		<value>User Interface</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RESET_TO_DEFAULTS">
		<value>Reset to Defaults</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_VIEW_BOBBING">
		<value>View Bobbing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HINTS">
		<value>Hints</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_IN_GAME_TOOLTIPS">
		<value>In-Game Tooltips</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHECKBOX_VERTICAL_SPLIT_SCREEN">
		<value>2 Player Split-screen Vertical</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DONE">
		<value>Done</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_EDIT_SIGN_MESSAGE">
		<value>Edit sign message:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SOCIAL_TEXT">
		<value>Fill in the details to accompany your screenshot</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SOCIAL_LABEL_CAPTION">
		<value>Caption</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SOCIAL_DEFAULT_CAPTION">
		<value>Screenshot from in-game</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SOCIAL_LABEL_DESCRIPTION">
		<value>Edit sign message:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEFAULT_TEXTUREPACK">
		<value>The classic Minecraft textures, icons and user interface!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNHIDE_MASHUP_WORLDS">
		<value>Show all Mash-up Worlds</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_EMPTY">
		<value>No Effects</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_MOVESPEED">
		<value>Speed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_MOVESLOWDOWN">
		<value>Slowness</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DIGSPEED">
		<value>Haste</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DIGSLOWDOWN">
		<value>Mining Fatigue</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DAMAGEBOOST">
		<value>Strength</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_WEAKNESS">
		<value>Weakness</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_HEAL">
		<value>Instant Health</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_HARM">
		<value>Instant Damage</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_JUMP">
		<value>Jump Boost</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_CONFUSION">
		<value>Nausea</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_REGENERATION">
		<value>Regeneration</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_RESISTANCE">
		<value>Resistance</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_FIRERESISTANCE">
		<value>Fire Resistance</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_WATERBREATHING">
		<value>Water Breathing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_INVISIBILITY">
		<value>Invisibility</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_BLINDNESS">
		<value>Blindness</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_NIGHTVISION">
		<value>Night Vision</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_HUNGER">
		<value>Hunger</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_POISON">
		<value>Poison</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_WITHER">
		<value>Wither</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_HEALTHBOOST">
		<value>Health Boost</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_ABSORPTION">
		<value>Absorption</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_SATURATION">
		<value>Saturation</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_MOVESPEED_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Swiftness</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_MOVESLOWDOWN_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Slowness</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DIGSPEED_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Haste</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DIGSLOWDOWN_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Dullness</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DAMAGEBOOST_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Strength</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_WEAKNESS_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Weakness</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_HEAL_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Healing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_HARM_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Harming</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_JUMP_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Leaping</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_CONFUSION_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Nausea</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_REGENERATION_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Regeneration</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_RESISTANCE_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Resistance</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_FIRERESISTANCE_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Fire Resistance</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_WATERBREATHING_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Water Breathing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_INVISIBILITY_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Invisibility</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_BLINDNESS_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Blindness</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_NIGHTVISION_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Night Vision</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_HUNGER_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Hunger</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_POISON_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Poison</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_WITHER_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Decay</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_HEALTHBOOST_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Health Boost</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_ABSORPTION_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Absorption</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_SATURATION_POSTFIX">
		<value>of Saturation</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_POTENCY_0">
		<value/>

	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_POTENCY_1">
		<value>II</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_POTENCY_2">
		<value>III</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_POTENCY_3">
		<value>IV</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_GRENADE">
		<value>Splash </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_MUNDANE">
		<value>Mundane </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_UNINTERESTING">
		<value>Uninteresting </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_BLAND">
		<value>Bland </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_CLEAR">
		<value>Clear </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_MILKY">
		<value>Milky </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_DIFFUSE">
		<value>Diffuse </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_ARTLESS">
		<value>Artless </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_THIN">
		<value>Thin </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_AWKWARD">
		<value>Awkward </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_FLAT">
		<value>Flat </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_BULKY">
		<value>Bulky </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_BUNGLING">
		<value>Bungling </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_BUTTERED">
		<value>Buttered </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_SMOOTH">
		<value>Smooth </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_SUAVE">
		<value>Suave </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_DEBONAIR">
		<value>Debonair </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_THICK">
		<value>Thick </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_ELEGANT">
		<value>Elegant </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_FANCY">
		<value>Fancy </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_CHARMING">
		<value>Charming </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_DASHING">
		<value>Dashing </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_REFINED">
		<value>Refined </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_CORDIAL">
		<value>Cordial </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_SPARKLING">
		<value>Sparkling </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_POTENT">
		<value>Potent </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_FOUL">
		<value>Foul </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_ODORLESS">
		<value>Odorless </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_RANK">
		<value>Rank </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_HARSH">
		<value>Harsh </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_ACRID">
		<value>Acrid </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_GROSS">
		<value>Gross </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_PREFIX_STINKY">
		<value>Stinky </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_WATER_BOTTLE">
		<value>Used as the base of all potions. Use in a brewing stand to create potions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_EMPTY">
		<value>Has no effects, can be used in a brewing stand to create potions by adding more ingredients.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_MOVESPEED">
		<value>Increases affected players, animals and monsters movement speed, and players sprinting speed, jumping length and field of view.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_MOVESLOWDOWN">
		<value>Reduces affected players, animals and monsters movement speed, and players sprinting speed, jumping length and field of view.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_DAMAGEBOOST">
		<value>Increase the damage caused by affected players and monsters when attacking.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_WEAKNESS">
		<value>Reduces the damage cause by affected players and monsters when attacking.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_HEAL">
		<value>Instantly increases the affected players, animals and monsters health.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_HARM">
		<value>Instantly reduces the affected players, animals and monsters health.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_REGENERATION">
		<value>Restores health to the affected players, animals and monsters over time.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_FIRERESISTANCE">
		<value>Makes the affected players, animals and monsters immune to damage from fire, lava, and ranged Blaze attacks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_POISON">
		<value>Reduces health of the affected players, animals and monsters over time.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_EFFECTS_WHENDRANK">
		<value>When Applied:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ATTRIBUTE_NAME_HORSE_JUMPSTRENGTH">
		<value>Horse Jump Strength</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ATTRIBUTE_NAME_ZOMBIE_SPAWNREINFORCEMENTS">
		<value>Zombie Reinforcements</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ATTRIBUTE_NAME_GENERIC_MAXHEALTH">
		<value>Max Health</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ATTRIBUTE_NAME_GENERIC_FOLLOWRANGE">
		<value>Mob Follow Range</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ATTRIBUTE_NAME_GENERIC_KNOCKBACKRESISTANCE">
		<value>Knockback Resistance</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ATTRIBUTE_NAME_GENERIC_MOVEMENTSPEED">
		<value>Speed</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ATTRIBUTE_NAME_GENERIC_ATTACKDAMAGE">
		<value>Attack Damage</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_DAMAGE_ALL">
		<value>Sharpness</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_DAMAGE_UNDEAD">
		<value>Smite</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_DAMAGE_ARTHROPODS">
		<value>Bane of Arthropods</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_KNOCKBACK">
		<value>Knockback</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_FIRE">
		<value>Fire Aspect</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_PROTECT_ALL">
		<value>Protection</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_PROTECT_FIRE">
		<value>Fire Protection</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_PROTECT_FALL">
		<value>Feather Falling</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_PROTECT_EXPLOSION">
		<value>Blast Protection</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_PROTECT_PROJECTILE">
		<value>Projectile Protection</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_OXYGEN">
		<value>Respiration</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_WATER_WORKER">
		<value>Aqua Affinity</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_DIGGING">
		<value>Efficiency</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_UNTOUCHING">
		<value>Silk Touch</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_DURABILITY">
		<value>Unbreaking</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LOOT_BONUS">
		<value>Looting</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LOOT_BONUS_DIGGER">
		<value>Fortune</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_ARROW_DAMAGE">
		<value>Power</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_ARROW_FIRE">
		<value>Flame</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_ARROW_KNOCKBACK">
		<value>Punch</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_ARROW_INFINITE">
		<value>Infinity</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_1">
		<value>I</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_2">
		<value>II</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_3">
		<value>III</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_4">
		<value>IV</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_5">
		<value>V</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_6">
		<value>VI</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_7">
		<value>VII</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_8">
		<value>VIII</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_9">
		<value>IX</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_LEVEL_10">
		<value>X</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_EMERALDORE">
		<value>Can be mined with an Iron pickaxe or better to collect Emeralds.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ENDERCHEST">
		<value>Similar to a Chest except that items placed in an Ender Chest are available in every one of the player's Ender Chests, even in different dimensions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_TRIPWIRE_SOURCE">
		<value>Is activated when an entity passes through a connected Tripwire.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_TRIPWIRE">
		<value>Activates a connected Tripwire Hook when an entity passes through it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_EMERALDBLOCK">
		<value>A compact way of storing Emeralds.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_COBBLESTONE_WALL">
		<value>A wall made of Cobblestone.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ANVIL">
		<value>Can be used to repair weapons, tools and armor.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_NETHER_QUARTZ_ORE">
		<value>Smelted in a furnace to produce Nether Quartz.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_QUARTZ_BLOCK">
		<value>Used as a decoration.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_EMERALD">
		<value>Can be traded with villagers.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_FLOWERPOT">
		<value>Used as a decoration. Flowers, Saplings, Cacti and Mushrooms can be planted in it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CARROTS">
		<value>Restores 2{*ICON_SHANK_01*}, and can be crafted into a golden carrot. Can be planted in farmland.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_POTATO">
		<value>Restores 0.5{*ICON_SHANK_01*}, or can be cooked in a furnace. This can be planted in farmland.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_POTATO_BAKED">
		<value>Restores 3{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Created by cooking a potato in a furnace.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_POTATO_POISONOUS">
		<value>Restores 1{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Eating this can cause you to become poisoned.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CARROT_GOLDEN">
		<value>Restores 3{*ICON_SHANK_01*}. Crafted from a carrot and gold nuggets.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CARROT_ON_A_STICK">
		<value>Used to control a saddled pig when riding on it.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_PUMPKIN_PIE">
		<value>Restores 4{*ICON_SHANK_01*}.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ENCHANTED_BOOK">
		<value>Used with an Anvil to enchant weapons, tools or armor.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_NETHER_QUARTZ">
		<value>Created by mining Nether Quartz Ore. Can be crafted into a Block of Quartz.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_CARPET">
		<value>Crafted from Wool. Used as a decoration.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_EMERALD">
		<value>Emerald</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FLOWERPOT">
		<value>Flower Pot</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CARROTS">
		<value>Carrot</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTATO">
		<value>Potato</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_POTATO_BAKED">
		<value>Baked Potato</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_POTATO_POISONOUS">
		<value>Poisonous Potato</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CARROT_GOLDEN">
		<value>Golden Carrot</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_CARROT_ON_A_STICK">
		<value>Carrot on a Stick</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_PUMPKIN_PIE">
		<value>Pumpkin Pie</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_ENCHANTED_BOOK">
		<value>Enchanted Book</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ITEM_NETHER_QUARTZ">
		<value>Nether Quartz</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_EMERALDORE">
		<value>Emerald Ore</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ENDERCHEST">
		<value>Ender Chest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_TRIPWIRE_SOURCE">
		<value>Tripwire Hook</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_TRIPWIRE">
		<value>Tripwire</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_EMERALDBLOCK">
		<value>Block of Emerald</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_COBBLESTONE_WALL">
		<value>Cobblestone Wall</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_COBBLESTONE_WALL_MOSSY">
		<value>Mossy Cobblestone Wall</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_FLOWERPOT">
		<value>Flower Pot</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARROTS">
		<value>Carrots</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_POTATOES">
		<value>Potatoes</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ANVIL">
		<value>Anvil</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ANVIL_INTACT">
		<value>Anvil</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ANVIL_SLIGHTLYDAMAGED">
		<value>Slightly Damaged Anvil</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_ANVIL_VERYDAMAGED">
		<value>Very Damaged Anvil</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_NETHER_QUARTZ">
		<value>Nether Quartz Ore</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_QUARTZ_BLOCK">
		<value>Block of Quartz</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_QUARTZ_BLOCK_CHISELED">
		<value>Chiseled Quartz Block</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_QUARTZ_BLOCK_LINES">
		<value>Pillar Quartz Block</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STAIRS_QUARTZ">
		<value>Quartz Stairs</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET">
		<value>Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_BLACK">
		<value>Black Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_RED">
		<value>Red Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_GREEN">
		<value>Green Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_BROWN">
		<value>Brown Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_BLUE">
		<value>Blue Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_PURPLE">
		<value>Purple Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_CYAN">
		<value>Cyan Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_SILVER">
		<value>Light Gray Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_GRAY">
		<value>Gray Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_PINK">
		<value>Pink Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_LIME">
		<value>Lime Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_YELLOW">
		<value>Yellow Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_LIGHT_BLUE">
		<value>Light Blue Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_MAGENTA">
		<value>Magenta Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_ORANGE">
		<value>Orange Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_CARPET_WHITE">
		<value>White Carpet</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SANDSTONE_CHISELED">
		<value>Chiseled Sandstone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_SANDSTONE_SMOOTH">
		<value>Smooth Sandstone</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_THORNS">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was killed trying to hurt {*SOURCE*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FALLING_ANVIL">
		<value>{*PLAYER*}  was squashed by a falling Anvil.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DEATH_FALLING_TILE">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} was squashed by a falling block.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_COMMAND_TELEPORT_SUCCESS">
		<value>Teleported {*PLAYER*} to {*DESTINATION*}</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_COMMAND_TELEPORT_ME">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} teleported you to their position</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_COMMAND_TELEPORT_TO_ME">
		<value>{*PLAYER*} teleported to you</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENCHANTMENT_THORNS">
		<value>Thorns</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TILE_STONESLAB_QUARTZ">
		<value>Quartz Slab</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_NIGHTVISION">
		<value>Makes dark areas appear as if in daylight, even under water.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_POTION_DESC_INVISIBILITY">
		<value>Makes affected players, animals and monsters invisible.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REPAIR_AND_NAME">
		<value>Repair &amp; Name</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REPAIR_COST">
		<value>Enchantment Cost: %d</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REPAIR_EXPENSIVE">
		<value>Too Expensive!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TITLE_RENAME">
		<value>Rename</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_YOU_HAVE">
		<value>You have:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_REQUIRED_ITEMS_FOR_TRADE">
		<value>Required Items For Trade</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_VILLAGER_OFFERS_ITEM">
		<value>{*VILLAGER_TYPE*} offers %s</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_REPAIR">
		<value>Repair</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_TRADE">
		<value>Trade</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_DYECOLLAR">
		<value>Dye collar</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			This is the Anvil interface, which you can use to rename, repair and apply enchantments to weapons, armor, or tools, at the cost of Experience Levels.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_ANVIL_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about the Anvil interface.{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know the Anvil interface.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_MENU_START">
		<value>
			To begin working on an item, place it in the first input slot. 
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_MENU_REPAIR">
		<value>
			When the correct raw material is placed in the second input slot (e.g. Iron Ingots for a damaged Iron Sword), the proposed repair appears in the output slot.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_MENU_SACRIFICE">
		<value>
			Alternatively, a second identical item can be placed into the second slot to combine the two items.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_MENU_ENCHANT">
		<value>
			To enchant items on the Anvil, place an Enchanted Book in the second input slot.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_MENU_COST">
		<value>
			The number of Experience Levels that the work will cost is shown beneath the output. If you do not have enough Experience Levels, the repair cannot be completed.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_MENU_RENAMING">
		<value>
			It is possible to rename the item by editing the name shown in the textbox.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_MENU_SMITH">
		<value>
			Picking up the repaired item will consume both items used by the Anvil and decrease your Experience Level by the given amount.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			In this area there is an Anvil and a Chest containing tools and weapons to work on.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_ANVIL_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about the Anvil.{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about the Anvil.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_SUMMARY">
		<value>
			Using an Anvil, weapons and tools can be repaired to restore their durability, renamed, or enchanted with Enchanted Books.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_ENCHANTED_BOOKS">
		<value>
			Enchanted Books can be found inside Chests within dungeons, or enchanted from normal Books at the Enchantment Table.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_COST">
		<value>
			Using the Anvil costs Experience Levels, and each use has a chance to damage the Anvil.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_COST2">
		<value>
			The type of work to be done, value of the item, number of enchantments, and amount of prior work all affect the cost of repair.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_RENAMING">
		<value>
			Renaming an item changes the displayed name for all players and permanently reduces the prior work cost.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ANVIL_USE_CHESTS">
		<value>
			In the Chest in this area you will find damaged Pickaxes, raw materials, Bottles O' Enchanting, and Enchanted Books to experiment with.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			This is the trading interface which displays trades that can be made with a villager.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_TRADING_MENU_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about the trading interface.{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know the trading interface.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_MENU_START">
		<value>
			All trades that the villager is willing to make at the moment are displayed along the top.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_MENU_UNAVAILABLE">
		<value>
			Trades will appear red and be unavailable if you do not have the required items.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_MENU_DETAILS">
		<value>
			The amount and type of items you are giving to the villager are shown in the two boxes on the left.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_MENU_INVENTORY">
		<value>
			You can see the total number of the items required for the trade in the two boxes on the left.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_MENU_TRADE">
		<value>
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to trade the items the villager requires for the item on offer.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			In this area there is a villager and a Chest containing Paper to purchase items.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_TRADING_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about trading.{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about trading.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_SUMMARY">
		<value>
			Players can trade items from their inventory with villagers.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_TRADES">
		<value>
			The trades a villager is likely to offer depends on their profession.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_INCREASE_TRADES">
		<value>
			Performing a mix of trades will randomly add to or update the villager's available trades.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_DECREASE_TRADES">
		<value>
			Trades that have been used frequently may be removed temporarily, but the villager will always offer at least one trade.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_TRADING_USE_CHESTS">
		<value>
			Take some Paper from the Chest and try trading with the villager here.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENDERCHEST_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			In this area there are two Ender Chests.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_PROMPT_ENDERCHEST_OVERVIEW">
		<value>
			{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_A*} to learn more about Ender Chests.{*B*}
			Press{*CONTROLLER_VK_B*} if you already know about Ender Chests.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENDERCHEST_SUMMARY">
		<value>
			All Ender Chests in a world are linked, even across dimensions. Items placed into an Ender Chest are accessible in any other Ender Chest.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENDERCHEST_PLAYERS">
		<value>
			However, the contents of the Ender Chests are different for each player.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENDERCHEST_FUNCTION">
		<value>
			This allows players to store items in any Ender Chest, and retrieve them from other Ender Chests in different positions in the world. You can try this now by placing items in either Ender Chest.
		</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_ENCHANTED_GOLDENAPPLE">
		<value>Restores 2{*ICON_SHANK_01*}, regenerates health for 30 seconds, and grants fire resistance and damage resistance for 5 minutes. Crafted from an apple and gold blocks.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ENABLE_TELEPORT">
		<value>Can Teleport</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TELEPORT">
		<value>Teleport</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TELEPORT_TO_PLAYER">
		<value>Teleport To Player</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TELEPORT_TO_ME">
		<value>Teleport To Me</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CAN_DISABLE_EXHAUSTION">
		<value>Can Disable Exhaustion</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CAN_INVISIBLE">
		<value>Can Become Invisible</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_CAN_INVISIBLE_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can now enable invisibility</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_CAN_INVISIBLE_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can no longer enable invisibility</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_CAN_FLY_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can now enable flying</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_CAN_FLY_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can no longer enable flying</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_CAN_EXHAUSTION_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can now disable exhaustion</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_CAN_EXHAUSTION_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can no longer disable exhaustion</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_CAN_TELEPORT_TOGGLE_ON">
		<value>You can now teleport</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_PRIV_CAN_TELEPORT_TOGGLE_OFF">
		<value>You can no longer teleport</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_ANVIL">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : ANVIL{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Experience Levels can be used to repair, enchant or rename items with the Anvil.{*B*}
All items can be renamed, although only items with durability can be repaired or have enchantments from Enchanted Books applied to them.{*B*}
An item can be repaired by placing it in one of the input slots on the left, along with either some raw materials of the item, like Iron Ingots for an Iron Sword, or combined with another item of the same type.{*B*}
Combining items is more efficient when done with an Anvil, and additionally, if either of the items were enchanted, the finished product may have enchantments from either of the inputs.{*B*}
Enchanted Books can apply enchantments to items by combining them at an Anvil if the Book's enchantment is suitable. Enchanted Books can be found in Chests within dungeons, or enchanted from normal Books at the Enchantment Table.{*B*}
There is a chance that the Anvil will be damaged with each use and after enough punishment it will be destroyed.{*B*}
    </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_TRADING">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : TRADING{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
It is possible to trade items with villagers. Each villager has a profession; they can be Farmers, Butchers, Blacksmiths, Librarians or Priests, and this affects the type of items they might trade.{*B*}
You can find a list of all the trades a villager is offering in the trading menu. A villager may modify or add to its trades whenever a player trades with it, although a trade might become temporarily disabled if it is used too frequently.{*B*}
Trades usually involve buying or selling a number of items for emeralds.{*B*}
If you do not have the items required for a trade, the items are shown in red.{*B*}
    </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_ENDERCHEST">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : ENDER CHEST {*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
All Ender Chests in a world are linked. Items placed into an Ender Chest are accessible in any other. However, the contents of the Ender Chests are different for each player. This allows players to store items in any Ender Chest, and retrieve them from other Ender Chests in different positions in the world.
  </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_VILLAGER_FARMER">
		<value>Farmer</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_VILLAGER_LIBRARIAN">
		<value>Librarian</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_VILLAGER_PRIEST">
		<value>Priest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_VILLAGER_SMITH">
		<value>Blacksmith</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_VILLAGER_BUTCHER">
		<value>Butcher</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_DESC_VILLAGER">
		<value>Found in villages, villagers will offer to sell items to the player depending on their profession.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHEST_LARGE">
		<value>Large Chest</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_ENCHANTING_BOOKS">
		<value>
	  You can also create Enchanted Books at the Enchantment Table, which can be used later at the Anvil to apply their enchantment to an item.
	</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_REDSTONE_TRIPWIRE">
		<value>
		Tripwire Hooks will also provide constant power to a circuit while something is triggering the string between them.
	</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREEDING_WOLF_COLLAR">
		<value>
        Once tamed, a wolf will always have its collar on. The color of their collar can be changed by dying it.
    </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FARMING_CARROTS_AND_POTATOES">
		<value>Carrots and Potatoes are farmed by planting Carrots or Potatoes, and are ready for harvesting when the vegetable is visible above the ground.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_BREEDING_RIDING_PIGS">
		<value>
        Additionally, pigs can be saddled and then ridden by players. They are controlled by tempting them with a Carrot on a Stick.
    </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_MINECART_PUSHING">
		<value>
      If necessary you can slowly move your minecart along using {*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*}. This helps to start the minecart by getting it onto a powered rail.
    </value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONNECTION_FAILED_NO_SD_SPLITSCREEN">
		<value>You cannot join this game as split-screen is only supported when in High Definition mode. Sign out all other players if you wish to join.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CURE">
		<value>Cure</value>
	</data>	
</root>