<root>
	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_0">
		<value>NOT USED</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_1">
		<value>You can use the touchscreen on the PlayStation®Vita system to navigate menus!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_48">
		<value>minecraftforum has a section dedicated to the PlayStation®Vita Edition.</value>
	</data>

  <data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_44">
    <value>You'll get the latest info on this game from @4JStudios and @Kappische on twitter!</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_TIPS_GAMETIP_45">
    <value>Don't look an Enderman in the eye!</value>
  </data>
  
	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_4">
		<value>We think 4J Studios has removed Herobrine from the PlayStation®Vita system game, but we're not too sure.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TIPS_TRIVIA_17">
		<value>Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition broke lots of records!</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_MULTIPLAYER">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : MULTIPLAYER{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
Minecraft on the PlayStation®Vita system is a multiplayer game by default.{*B*}{*B*}
When you start or join an online game, it will be visible to people in your friends list (unless you've selected Invite Only when hosting the game), and if they join the game, it will also be visible to people in their friends list (if you have selected the Allow Friends of Friends option).{*B*}
When you are in a game, you can press the SELECT button to bring up a list of all other players in the game, and Kick players from the game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_SOCIALMEDIA">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : SHARING SCREENSHOTS{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
You can capture a screenshot from your game by bringing up the Pause Menu, and pressing{*CONTROLLER_VK_Y*} to Share to Facebook. You'll be presented with a miniature version of your screenshot, and can edit the text associated with the Facebook post.{*B*}{*B*}
There's a camera mode especially for taking these screenshots, so that you can see the front of your character in the shot - press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_CAMERA*} until you can see the front view of your character before pressing{*CONTROLLER_VK_Y*} to Share.{*B*}{*B*}
Online ID's will not be displayed in the screenshot.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_HOW_TO_PLAY_CREATIVE">
		<value>{*T3*}HOW TO PLAY : CREATIVE MODE{*ETW*}{*B*}{*B*}
The creative mode interface allows any item in the game to be moved into the player’s inventory without the need for mining or crafting the item. 
The items in the player's inventory will not be removed when they are placed or used in the world, and this allows the player to focus on building rather than resource gathering.{*B*}
If you create, load or save a world in Creative Mode, that world will have trophies and leaderboard updates disabled, even if it is then loaded in Survival Mode.{*B*}
To fly when in Creative Mode, press{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_JUMP*} twice quickly. To exit flying, repeat the action. To fly faster, push{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*} forward twice in rapid succession while flying. 
When in flying mode, you can hold down{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_JUMP*} to move up and{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_SNEAK*} to move down, or use{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_DPAD_UP*} to move up, {*CONTROLLER_ACTION_DPAD_DOWN*} to move down, 
{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_DPAD_LEFT*} to move left, and {*CONTROLLER_ACTION_DPAD_RIGHT*} to move right.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TUTORIAL_TASK_FLY">
		<value>Pressing{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_JUMP*} twice quickly will allow you to fly. To exit flying, repeat the action. To fly faster, push{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_MOVE*} forward twice in rapid succession while flying. 
When in flying mode, you can hold down{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_JUMP*} to move up and{*CONTROLLER_ACTION_SNEAK*} to move down, or use the directional buttons to move up, down, left or right.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SELECTDEVICE">
		<value>NOT USED</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_CHANGEDEVICE">
		<value>NOT USED</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_VIEW_GAMERCARD">
		<value>"NOT USED"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_VIEW_GAMERPROFILE">
		<value>"NOT USED"</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_INVITE_PARTY">
		<value>Invite Friends</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_START_CREATIVE">
		<value>If you create, load or save a world in Creative Mode, that world will have trophies and leaderboard updates disabled, even if it is then loaded in Survival Mode. Are you sure you want to continue?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_START_SAVEDINCREATIVE">
		<value>This world has previously been saved in Creative Mode, and it will have trophies and leaderboard updates disabled. Are you sure you want to continue?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_START_SAVEDINCREATIVE_CONTINUE">
		<value>This world has previously been saved in Creative Mode, and it will have trophies and leaderboard updates disabled.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONFIRM_START_HOST_PRIVILEGES">
		<value>If you create, load or save a world with Host Privileges enabled, that world will have trophies and leaderboard updates disabled, even if it is then loaded with those options off. Are you sure you want to continue?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONNECTION_LOST_LIVE">
		<value>Connection to "PSN" was lost. Exiting to the main menu.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CONNECTION_LOST_LIVE_NO_EXIT">
		<value>Connection to "PSN" was lost.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_ACHIEVEMENT_TEXT">
		<value>This is the Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition trial game. If you had the full game, you would just have earned a trophy!
Unlock the full game to experience the joy of Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition and to play with your friends across the globe through "PSN".
Would you like to unlock the full game?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_THEME_TEXT">
		<value>This is the Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition trial game. If you had the full game, you would just have earned a theme!
Unlock the full game to experience the joy of Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition and to play with your friends across the globe through "PSN".
Would you like to unlock the full game?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_ACCEPT_INVITE">
		<value>This is the Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition trial game. You need the full game to be able to accept this invite.
Would you like to unlock the full game?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_UNLOCK_GUEST_TEXT">
		<value>Guest players cannot unlock the full game. Please sign in with a Sony Entertainment Network account.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LEADERBOARD_GAMERTAG">
		<value>Online ID</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GROUPNAME_POTIONS_480">
		<value>Brewing</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_RETURNEDTOTITLESCREEN_TEXT">
		<value>You have been returned to the title screen because you have been signed out of the "PSN".
</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_TRIALOVER_TEXT">
		<value>You've been playing the Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition Trial Game for the maximum time allowed! To continue the fun, would you like to unlock the full game?</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_FATAL_ERROR_TEXT">
		<value>"Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition" has failed to load, and cannot continue.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NO_MULTIPLAYER_PRIVILEGE_JOIN_TEXT">
		<value>Failed to join the game as one or more players are not allowed to play Online due to their Sony Entertainment Network account chat restrictions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NO_MULTIPLAYER_PRIVILEGE_HOST_TEXT">
		<value>Failed to create an online game as one or more players are not allowed to play Online due to their Sony Entertainment Network account chat restrictions. Uncheck the "Online Game" box in "More Options" to start an offline game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NO_USER_CREATED_CONTENT_PRIVILEGE_SINGLE_LOCAL">
		<value>You are not allowed to join this game session because Online is disabled on your Sony Entertainment Network account due to chat restrictions.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NO_USER_CREATED_CONTENT_PRIVILEGE_ALL_LOCAL">
		<value>You are not allowed to join this game session because one of your local players has Online disabled on their Sony Entertainment Network account due to chat restrictions. Uncheck the "Online Game" box in "More Options" to start an offline game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_NO_USER_CREATED_CONTENT_PRIVILEGE_CREATE">
		<value>You are not allowed to create this game session because one of your local players has Online disabled on their Sony Entertainment Network account due to chat restrictions. Uncheck the "Online Game" box in "More Options" to start an offline game.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SAVE_ICON_MESSAGE">
		<value>This game has a level autosave feature. When you see the icon above displayed, the game is saving your data.
Please do not turn off your PlayStation®Vita system while this icon is on-screen.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_GAMEOPTION_HOST_PRIVILEGES">
		<value>When enabled, the host can toggle their ability to fly, disable exhaustion, and make themselves invisible from the in-game menu. Disables trophies and leaderboard updates.</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_CHECKBOX_DISPLAY_SPLITSCREENGAMERTAGS">
		<value>Splitscreen Online ID's</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_ACHIEVEMENTS">
		<value>Trophies</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_LABEL_GAMERTAGS">
		<value>Online ID's:</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_IN_GAME_GAMERTAGS">
		<value>In-Game Online ID's</value>
	</data>	

	<data name="IDS_SOCIAL_DEFAULT_DESCRIPTION">
		<value>Look what I made in Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition!</value>
	</data>

  <data name="IDS_USING_TRIAL_TEXUREPACK_WARNING">
    <value>You are using the trial version of a texture pack. You will have access to the full contents of the texture pack, but you will not be able to save your progress.
If you try to save while using the trial version, you will be given the option to purchase the full version.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_TITLE_UPDATE_NAME">
    <value>Patch 1.04 (Title Update 14)</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_BACK_BUTTON">
    <value>SELECT</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_HOST_OPTION_DISABLES_ACHIEVEMENTS">
    <value>This option disables trophies and leaderboard updates for this world while playing, and if loading it again after saving with this option on.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_SIGNIN_PSN">
    <value>Would you like to sign in to the "PSN"?</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_KICK_PLAYER_DESCRIPTION">
    <value>For players that are not on the same PlayStation®Vita system as the host player, selecting this option will kick the player from the game and any other players on their PlayStation®Vita system. This player will not be able to rejoin the game until it is restarted.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_PLATFORM_NAME">
    <value>PlayStation®Vita</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_TOOLTIP_CHANGE_NETWORK_MODE">
    <value>Change Network Mode</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_SELECT_NETWORK_MODE_TITLE">
    <value>Select Network Mode</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_SELECT_NETWORK_MODE_TEXT">
    <value>Choose Ad Hoc Network to connect with other PlayStation®Vita systems nearby, or "PSN" to connect with friends all over the world.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_NETWORK_ADHOC">
    <value>Ad Hoc Network</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS__NETWORK_PSN">
    <value>"PSN"</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SAVETRANSFER_DOWNLOAD">
    <value>Download PS3™ Save</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_TOOLTIPS_SAVETRANSFER_UPLOAD">
    <value>Upload Save for PS3™/PS4™</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_CANCEL_UPLOAD_TITLE">
    <value>Upload Canceled</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_CANCEL_UPLOAD_TEXT">
    <value>You have canceled uploading this save to the save transfer area.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_SAVETRANSFER_STAGE_PUT_DATA">
    <value>Uploading data : %d%%</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_SAVETRANSFER_STAGE_GET_DATA">
    <value>Downloading data : %d%%</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_SAVE_TRANSFER_TEXT">
    <value>Are you sure you would like to upload this save, and overwrite any current save held in the save transfer area?</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_SAVETRANSFER_STAGE_CONVERTING">
    <value>Converting Data</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_SAVETRANSFER_STAGE_SAVING">
    <value>Saving</value>
  </data>
  <data name="IDS_SAVE_TRANSFER_UPLOADCOMPLETE">
    <value>Upload Complete!</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_SAVE_TRANSFER_UPLOADFAILED">
    <value>Upload Failed. Please try again later.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_SAVE_TRANSFER_DOWNLOADCOMPLETE">
    <value>Download Complete!</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_SAVE_TRANSFER_DOWNLOADFAILED">
    <value>Download Failed. Please try again later.</value>
  </data>
  
  
  <data name="IDS_DISCONNECTED_NAT_TYPE_MISMATCH">
    <value>Failed to join the game due to a restrictive NAT type. Please check your network settings.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_SAVE_TRANSFER_NOT_AVAILABLE_TEXT">
    <value>
There is no save available in the save transfer area at the moment.
You can upload a world save to the save transfer area using Minecraft: PlayStation®3 Edition, and then download it with Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition.
    </value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_SAVE_TRANSFER_WRONG_VERSION">
    <value>The save file in the save transfer area has a version number that Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition doesn't support yet.</value>
  </data>

  <data name="IDS_SAVE_INCOMPLETE_TITLE">
    <value>Saving incomplete</value>
  </data>
  
  <data name="IDS_SAVE_INCOMPLETE_EXPLANATION_QUOTA">
    <value>Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition is out of space for save data. To make room, delete other Minecraft: PlayStation®Vita Edition saves.</value>
  </data>
  
</root>